<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<openerp>
    <data noupdate="1">

        <record id="demo_followup1" model="account_followup.followup">
            <field name="name">Default Follow-Up</field>
            <field name="company_id" ref="base.main_company"/>
            <field name="description">First letter after 15 net days, 30 net days and 45 days end of month levels.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="demo_followup_line1" model="account_followup.followup.line">
            <field name="name">Level 0 : 15 net days</field>
            <field name="sequence">0</field>
            <field name="start">days</field>
            <field name="delay">15</field>
            <field name="followup_id" ref="demo_followup1"/>
            <field name="description">
Dear %(partner_name)s,

Exception made if there was a mistake of ours, it seems that the following amount stays unpaid. Please, take appropriate measures in order to carry out this payment in the next 8 days.

Would your payment have been carried out after this mail was sent, please ignore this message. Do not hesitate to contact our accounting department at (+32).10.68.94.39.

Best Regards,
</field>
        </record>

        <record id="demo_followup_line2" model="account_followup.followup.line">
            <field name="name">Level 1 : 30 net days</field>
            <field name="sequence">1</field>
            <field name="start">days</field>
            <field name="delay">30</field>
            <field name="followup_id" ref="demo_followup1"/>
            <field name="description">
Dear %(partner_name)s,

We are disappointed to see that despite sending a reminder, that your account is now seriously overdue.

It is essential that immediate payment is made, otherwise we will have to consider placing a stop on your account which means that we will no longer be able to supply your company with (goods/services).
Please, take appropriate measures in order to carry out this payment in the next 8 days.

If there is a problem with paying invoice that we are not aware of, do not hesitate to contact our accounting department at (+32).10.68.94.39. so that we can resolve the matter quickly.

Details of due payments is printed below.

Best Regards,
</field>
        </record>

        <record id="demo_followup_line3" model="account_followup.followup.line">
            <field name="name">Level 2 : 45 days end of month</field>
            <field name="sequence">2</field>
            <field name="start">end_of_month</field>
            <field name="delay">45</field>
            <field name="followup_id" ref="demo_followup1"/>
            <field name="description">
Dear %(partner_name)s,

Despite several reminders, your account is still not settled.

Unless full payment is made in next 8 days, then legal action for the recovery of the debt will be taken without further notice.

I trust that this action will prove unnecessary and details of due payments is printed below.

In case of any queries concerning this matter, do not hesitate to contact our accounting department at (+32).10.68.94.39.

Best Regards,
</field>
        </record>

    </data>
</openerp>
