<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<openerp>
    <!-- <data noupdate="1"> -->
    <data>

        <!-- TAGS -->
        <record id="blog_tag_1" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">functional</field>
        </record>
        <record id="blog_tag_2" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">pos</field>
        </record>

        <!-- POSTS -->
        <record id="blog_post_1" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">OpenERP 7.0 Functional Demo</field>
            <field name="category_id" ref="blog_category_1"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_1')])]"/>
            <field name="content">
<![CDATA[<p>The news is out, OpenERP's latest version 7.0 is here.  It's more
user-friendly, even more business oriented and efficient to manage your company.</p>
<p>How to discover the latest version 6.1.?</p>
<ul>
    <li>
        Demo : <a target="http://demo.openerp.com" href="http://demo.openerp.com" style="background: url(&quot;data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAAoAAAAKCAYAAACNMs+9AAAAGXRFWHRTb2Z0d2FyZQBBZG9iZSBJbWFnZVJlYWR5ccllPAAAAFZJREFUeF59z4EJADEIQ1F36k7u5E7ZKXeUQPACJ3wK7UNokVxVk9kHnQH7bY9hbDyDhNXgjpRLqFlo4M2GgfyJHhjq8V4agfrgPQX3JtJQGbofmCHgA/nAKks+JAjFAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC&quot;) no-repeat scroll right center transparent;padding-right: 13px;">
    </li><li>
        Online: <a target="http://openerp.com/online" href="http://openerp.com/online" style="background: url(&quot;data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAAoAAAAKCAYAAACNMs+9AAAAGXRFWHRTb2Z0d2FyZQBBZG9iZSBJbWFnZVJlYWR5ccllPAAAAFZJREFUeF59z4EJADEIQ1F36k7u5E7ZKXeUQPACJ3wK7UNokVxVk9kHnQH7bY9hbDyDhNXgjpRLqFlo4M2GgfyJHhjq8V4agfrgPQX3JtJQGbofmCHgA/nAKks+JAjFAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC&quot;) no-repeat scroll right center transparent;padding-right: 13px;">
    </li><li>
        Download: <a target="http://openerp.com/downloads" href="http://openerp.com/downloads" style="background: url(&quot;data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAAoAAAAKCAYAAACNMs+9AAAAGXRFWHRTb2Z0d2FyZQBBZG9iZSBJbWFnZVJlYWR5ccllPAAAAFZJREFUeF59z4EJADEIQ1F36k7u5E7ZKXeUQPACJ3wK7UNokVxVk9kHnQH7bY9hbDyDhNXgjpRLqFlo4M2GgfyJHhjq8V4agfrgPQX3JtJQGbofmCHgA/nAKks+JAjFAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC&quot;) no-repeat scroll right center transparent;padding-right: 13px;"></a>
    </li>
</ul>
<p>We have also put together a functional demo that presents 6.1. Watch this video
to learn directly from us what OpenERP 6.1. can do for you. Share it in your
company, with your clients and implement it now for your business.</p>
<h3>Watch on Youtube!</h3>
<iframe width="480" height="390" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/7jES2jxKMso " frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe>
]]>
</field>
        </record>

        <record id="blog_post_2" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">Personalise Dashboards</field>
            <field name="category_id" ref="blog_category_1"/>
            <field name="content">
<![CDATA[
<p>You like OpenERP, but feel like you want to personalise it more? Now, OpenERP
goes a step further and lets you customize your dashboard.  Thanks to a new
feature that allows you to customize your dashboard by adding new boards of any
search view.</p>
<h3>How is it done?</h3>
<ul>
    <li>Step 1: access one search view</li>
    <li>Step 2: apply the filter you want to see at each connection to the application
(eg. on sales, manufacturing, etc)</li>
    <li>Step 3: add it into the dashboard in the same space where you can save the filter</li>
    <li>Step 4: choose the application you want it visible on and the name of the array</li>
</ul>
<p>Look at this simple example below from Purchase, where I want to put on the
application's dashboard "Purchases to Approve". After I access the search view
and apply the filter for "Purchases to Approve", I can add it immediately to my
Purchase dashboard.</p>
<img src="http://www.openerp.com/sites/default/files/fileattach/dashboard2_1(1).png" alt="">
<p>In less than a minute, the search view is visible on the dashboard</p>
<img src="http://www.openerp.com/sites/default/files/fileattach/dashboard2_2.png" alt="">
<p>Of course, you are free to delete what you don't need or like, but just in case<br>
you change your mind there is a reset button to return to the default view.</p>
]]>
</field>
        </record>

        <record id="blog_post_3" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">Touchscreen Point of Sale</field>
            <field name="category_id" ref="blog_category_1"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_1'), ref('blog_tag_2')])]"/>
            <field name="content">
<![CDATA[<p>The brand new OpenERP touchscreen point of sale available with 6.1 allows you
to manage your shop sales very easily.  It's fully web based so that you don't
have to install or deploy any software and all the sales shops can be easily
consolidated.  It works in connected and disconnected modes so that you can
continue to sell if you lose your internet connection.</p>
<img src="http://www.openerp.com/sites/default/files/fileattach/POS(2).png" alt="">
<h3>Here's a summary of its main features and benefits:</h3>
<ul>
    <li>100% WEB based</li>
    <li>available for any touchscreen device (ipod, ipad, any tablet)mobile (with portable devices)</li>
    <li>no installation required</li>
    <li>no synchronization needed, completely integrated</li>
    <li>continue working even when your connection is down if you close your browser, data won't be lost</li>
    <li>fully web based with a clean interface smart interface</li>
</ul>
<p>You have different options to select your products. You can do it through the
barcode reader, just browse through the categories you have put in place (ie.
drinks, snacks, meals, etc.), or text search in case neither of the other
options work for you.  If you need to use the POS for your restaurant, for
example, your employees can record at the same time multiple tickets without
having to wait to do one transaction at a time. Along, to facilitate payment,
the application allows multiple payment methods.</p>
<p>The POS application is so simple and accessible to use that your shop or
restaurant will never need any other tool to manage orders. Due to its smart
and user-friendly interface you don't need any training to learn how to use it.
Think of it as an out-of-the-box solution to boost your business' productivity.
</p>
]]>
</field>
        </record>

    </data>
</openerp>
