<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<openerp>
    <data>

        <record id="question_0" model="website.forum.post">
            <field name="name">How to configure alerts for employee contract expiration.</field>
            <field name="views">45</field>
        </record>
        
        <record id="question_1" model="website.forum.post">
            <field name="name">How to get translated state through browse ?</field>
             <field name="body">Hello everybody,

I use a XML-RPC to access to invoices, I want to get the states of invoices, but always I get paid instead of Payé (French)</field>
            <field name="views">45</field>
        </record>
        
        <record id="question_2" model="website.forum.post">
            <field name="name">Restrain the user from confirming the Purchase requisition</field>
            <field name="views">45</field>
            <field name="body">Can anybody tell me how to restrict the user from confirming the purchase requisition? In my case when a user is creating a purchase requisition than the user after saving it is able to send it to the supplier rather I want the user to just generate the purchase requisition and let the manager do the remaining works like sending the purchase requisition to the supplier and than receiving the goods. Please help me out. Thanks in advance.</field>
        </record>
        
        <record id="question_4" model="website.forum.post">
            <field name="name">Offline installing for add-ons</field>
            <field name="views">45</field>
            <field name="body">How can I install web based addons without Internet connections (I'm using OpenERP over LAN)?

P.S.

AFAIK current version (7.x) supports web interface while the desktop clients became deprecated.
BTW, I left OpenERP since ver. 6.x to use PostBooks instead but I recently decided to use OpenERP once again after recent new features.</field>
        </record>
        
        <record id="question_5" model="website.forum.post">
            <field name="name">CMS replacement for ERP and eCommerce</field>
            <field name="views">45</field>
            <field name="body">I use Wordpress as a CMS and eCommerce platform. The developing in Wordpress is too easy and solid but it missing ERP feature (there is single plugin to integrate with Frontaccounting) so I wonder:

Can I use OpenERP as a replacement CMS of Wordpress + eCommerce plugin?

In simple words does OpenERP became CMS+ERP platform?</field>
        </record>
        
        <record id="question_6" model="website.forum.post">
            <field name="name">Register payment using XMLRPC</field>
            <field name="views">45</field>
            <field name="body">Hi there,

I have been trying to register an invoice payment through OpenERP. I have been able to manually create and approve the invoice, the voucher and its line

I'm currently creating the voucher using this information:</field>
        </record>
        
        <record id="question_7" model="website.forum.post">
            <field name="name">Create one field on two modules</field>
            <field name="views">45</field>
            <field name="body">Hello,

I shall like creating a field "x" on an order form ( stock.picking.form ) and to reveal it also on the delivery slip ( stock.picking.form ).

Thank you in advance</field>
        </record>
        
        <record id="question_8" model="website.forum.post">
            <field name="name">access rights to one2many field</field>
            <field name="views">45</field>
            <field name="body">Now i create new group , assign user and access right as READ &amp; CREATE to object stock.picking.ads but nothing is reflected , iam able to delete and write which should not happen. Very Strange!!!</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</openerp>
