<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<templates>
    <t t-name="AdyenAccountCreationConfirmation">
        <main>
            <div class="alert alert-info">
                You can start processing payments as soon as your application is sent.<br/>
                Payouts will be blocked until your application has been accepted.<br/>
                We will notify you when the status of the review changes, or if additional data is required.<br/>
            </div>

            <h3>Submitted data</h3>
            <table class="table table-sm">
                <t t-if="data.is_business">
                    <tr>
                        <td>Legal Entity</td>
                        <td>Business</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Legal Business Name</td>
                        <td t-esc="data.legal_business_name"/>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Doing Business As</td>
                        <td t-esc="data.doing_business_as"/>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Registration Number</td>
                        <td t-esc="data.registration_number"/>
                    </tr>
                </t>
                <t t-else="">
                    <tr>
                        <td>Legal Entity</td>
                        <td>Individual</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>First Name</td>
                        <td t-esc="data.first_name"/>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Last Name</td>
                        <td t-esc="data.last_name"/>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Date of Birth</td>
                        <td t-esc="data.date_of_birth.format('YYYY-MM-DD')"/>
                    </tr>
                </t>
                <tr>
                    <td>Email</td>
                    <td t-esc="data.email"/>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>Phone Number</td>
                    <td t-esc="data.phone_number"/>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>Address</td>
                    <td>
                        <t t-esc="data.street"/> <t t-esc="data.house_number_or_name"/>,
                        <t t-esc="data.city"/> <t t-if="data.state_code" t-esc="data.state_code"/> <t t-esc="data.zip"/>,
                        <t t-esc="data.country_code"/>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>

            <h3>Disclaimers</h3>
            <p>WARNING: Please note that the right to use the payment services is only for
            sales in your own name. You may not resell, hire or on any other basis allow third
            parties to use the payment services to enable such third parties to be paid for their
            services. You may not use the payment services for different types of product and
            services than as registered with your application. In particular you confirm that you
            will not use the payment services for any type of product or service appearing in the
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/odoo_adyen/static/src/pdf/marketpay_prohibited_products_and_services.pdf">
            Prohibited Products and Services List of our Processor</a>. If we or our
            Processor at any time discover that the information you provided about your
            business is incorrect or has changed without informing us or if you violate any of
            these conditions, the services may be suspended and/or terminated with
            immediate effect and fines may be applied by the Credit Card Schemes and/or the
            authorities for unregistered or inappropriate use of payment services which will in
            such case be payable by you.</p>

            <h3>Contractual Relationship</h3>
            <p>The payment processing services ordered by you by placing this order will be
            provided to you by Adyen N.V. (hereafter “Processor”), with which you are
            entering into a direct agreement by confirming this order. Odoo S.A.
            (hereafter “We /Us”) will assist and support you in your use of the services to be
            provided by the Processor and we will provide you first line assistance with and
            enable you to connect to the systems of Processor to be able to use its services.
            For this purpose, you hereby instruct Processor to provide us access to your data
            and setting in Processor’s systems which are used by Processor to provide the
            services and authorise us to manage these on your behalf.</p>

            <h3>Pricing</h3>
            <ul>
                <li>Payment and processing fees are listed on <a href="http://www.adyen.com/pricing">adyen.com/pricing</a>.</li>
                <li>Payouts cost 0.20€ (EU) or 0.22$ (US) each.</li>
                <li>Chargebacks cost 7.5€ each.</li>
                <li>Onboarding and KYC cost 5€.</li>
            </ul>

            <input type="checkbox" class="opt_in_checkbox"/>
            I confirm I have taken notice of and accept the following terms and restrictions:
            <ul>
                <li>Adyen MarketPay Terms and Conditions (click <a href="https://www.odoo.com/odoo_adyen/static/src/pdf/marketpay_terms_and_conditions.pdf">here</a> to download and review)</li>
                <li>Adyen Restricted and Prohibited Products and Services list (click <a href="https://www.odoo.com/odoo_adyen/static/src/pdf/marketpay_prohibited_products_and_services.pdf">here</a> to download and review)</li>
            </ul>
        </main>
    </t>

    <t t-name="AdyenKYCStatusTag">
        <t t-if="value === 'awaiting_data'">
            <span class="badge badge-pill badge-warning">Data to provide</span>
        </t>
        <t t-if="value === 'pending'">
            <span class="badge badge-pill badge-info">Waiting for validation</span>
        </t>
        <t t-if="value === 'passed'">
            <span class="badge badge-pill badge-success">Confirmed</span>
        </t>
        <t t-if="value === 'failed'">
            <span class="badge badge-pill badge-danger">Failed</span>
        </t>
    </t>
</templates>
