<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<openerp>
    <data>

    <record id="base.res_partner_9" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_published">True</field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_12" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_published">True</field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_13" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_published">True</field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_22" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_published">True</field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_23" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_published">True</field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_5" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_published">True</field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_11" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_published">True</field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_2" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_published">True</field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_18" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_published">True</field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_10" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_published">True</field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_17" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">En Nebulosa de negocios contamos con más de 20 años de trabajo en el campo de la “Ingeniería de Software”. A lo largo de este tiempo hemos atendido a una importante cantidad de clientes, pertenecientes a una diversa gama...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[En Nebulosa de negocios contamos con más de 20 años de trabajo en el campo de la “Ingeniería de Software”.<br />

A lo largo de este tiempo hemos atendido a una importante cantidad de clientes, pertenecientes a una diversa gama de problemáticas.<br />

Con nuestra asistencia hemos cubierto las distintas fases que conforman un proyecto, con una metodología que ubica al Usuario como centro y actor privilegiado del proceso.
<br />
Esta trayectoria nos ubica en inmejorables condiciones para liderar proyectos de implementación, capacitación y customización de OpenERP.]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_2" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">Agrolait est un prestataire spécialisé depuis 10 ans dans la mise en oeuvre de solutions open source ERP, BI et e-commerce. Agrolait compte 100 collaborateurs basés en France, Belgique, Luxembourg et Suisse. For...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[Agrolait est un prestataire spécialisé depuis 10 ans dans la mise en oeuvre de solutions open source ERP, BI et e-commerce. Audaxis compte 100 collaborateurs basés en France, Belgique, Luxembourg et Suisse.<br /> <br />
 
Forts de 20 ans d’expérience dans les solutions ERP, nos consultants combinent expertise technologique, applicative et métier, afin de vous apporter un conseil éclairé tout au long de votre projet OpenERP. <br /> <br />
 
Notre méthodologie de projet, conçue pour les PME/PMI, est une garantie d'assurance qualité : architecture, installation, intégration, personnalisation, formation, suivi de projet, support, maintenance, et migration, notre engagement à vos côtés est total. <br /> <br />

Partenaire CTP Premium, Agrolait est certifié par OpenERP pour donner des formations fonctionnelles et techniques en France et en Tunisie. <br /> <br />
 
Nous intervenons sur plusieurs secteurs d'activité : distribution, retail, industrie, services, associations, avec une forte expertise sur le supply chain management (SCM) et les spécificités comptables pour le marché belge et français. Fort de son pôle d’expertise web, Agrolait vous fait aussi bénéficier des meilleurs conseils dans l’intégration d’OpenERP avec des portails.]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_24" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">OpenCorp est une société de services IT spécialisée dans l’intégration de solutions opensource hébergées dans le cloud à destination des PME, TPE, startups et des professions libérales.Au vu des avancées technologiques...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[OpenCorp est une société de services IT spécialisée dans l’intégration de solutions opensource hébergées dans le cloud à destination des PME, TPE, startups et des professions libérales.<br /> <br />

Au vu des avancées technologiques qui ont modifié en profondeur les attentes des utilisateurs et des pressions toujours plus importantes sur les budgets, OpenCorp est conscient que le niveau d'exigence des clients n'a jamais été aussi élevé. <br /> <br />

Fort de plus de 20 années d’expérience dans les systèmes d'informations, les fondateurs d'OpenCorp se sont donnés comme mission de bousculer le marché en s'appuyant sur un catalogue de solutions efficaces, stables et abordables afin de permettre à ses clients de gagner en compétitivité. <br /> <br />

C'est dans cette optique qu'OpenCorp est aujourd'hui un des premier resellers de la solution OpenERP 7.0 en mode SaaS. Notre philosophie "back to the standards" permet de réduire significativement les coûts liés à l'implémentation des projets. <br /> <br />

Experts en business analysis, nos consultants vous accompagneront également dans l'analyse de vos besoins en documentant vos processus, en identifiant les possibilités d'amélioration et en préparant les mandats de vos projets. <br /> <br />

Avec OpenCorp, vous avez la garantie d’une mise en œuvre maîtrisée d’un point de vue opérationnel et budgétaire.]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_3" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">China Export is committed to deliver a complete integrated business solution to fulfill your business requirements and meet your ever changing needs. China Export partners with OpenERP to build a feature rich, extensible...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[China Export is committed to deliver a complete integrated business solution to fulfill your business requirements and meet your ever changing needs. China Export partners with OpenERP to build a feature rich, extensible and cost-effective system for small and medium sized businesses. China Export’s commission is to help you build such a system for your company by leveraging a cost-effective open source software (OpenERP), our experienced consulting and services to keep your projects on-target and within budget, and an approach to support that ensure high-responsiveness.]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_25" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">Míng is a consulting firm with expertise in Finance and in Business Intelligence. (1) Outsourced financial director: implementation of flexible and customized data management system, financial reporting and KPI for an...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[Míng is a consulting firm with expertise in Finance and in Business Intelligence.<br />
 
(1) <b>Outsourced financial director: </b>implementation of flexible and customized data management system, financial reporting and KPI for an easy decision making process. <br />

(2) <b>Outsourced financial task force: </b>set-up of business plan, zero budget, company valuation, audits on internal controlling. <br />

(3) <b>All-included administrative and financial support package:</b> <br/>
a. Setting-up: support for getting the relevant business license and meeting the associated administrative PRC requirements. <br/>
b. Management: definition and implementation of procedures, proposal on the company organization. <br/>
c. Finance: bookkeeping, tax declaration, financial reporting and key indicators. <br/>
d. Decisional Information System: set-up of server, network, implementation of a customized data management system (OpenERP, Excel). <br/>
e. Human resources: recruitment, payroll management.]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_13" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">Axelor est une société de services spécialisée dans l'intégration d'ERP Open Source. Elle est notamment coéditrice de la version web de Open ERP et concentre toutes ses activités aux projets d'intégration de Open ERP...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[Axelor est une société de services spécialisée dans l'intégration d'ERP Open Source.
Elle est notamment coéditrice de la version web de Open ERP et concentre toutes ses activités aux projets d'intégration de Open ERP et de la mise en place de l'offre Saas (ASP) basée sur Open ERP. Axelor peut se prévaloir aujourd'hui de nombreuses références d'implémentations de Open ERP dans divers secteurs d'activités.<br/> <br/>
La société possède son propre centre de R&amp;D réalisant de nombreuses innovations permettant l'amélioration constante de Open ERP, telles que la nouvelle version web, les plug-In MS office et des connecteurs vers d'autres applications. Ses principaux atouts sont sa méthodologie d'intégration et sa rigueur permettant la prise en charge de grands projets depuis la phase d'audit et de conception jusqu'à  la mise en production et l'accompagnement client.]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_12" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">Créée en 2001, Camptocamp est Gold Partner OpenERP depuis 2006 en Suisse, France et Autriche et compte près de 50 collaborateurs tous professionnels de l'Open Source.Camptocamp est spécialisé dans l'imp...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[Créée en 2001, Camptocamp est Gold Partner OpenERP depuis 2006 en Suisse, France et Autriche et compte près de 50 collaborateurs tous professionnels de l'Open Source. <br/> <br/>
Camptocamp est spécialisé dans l'implémentation d'OpenERP au sein de sociétés de 10 à plusieurs centaines de collaborateurs dans les secteurs suivants :<br/>
<ul><li>négoce (achat/vente/stock), en particulier le domaine du e-commerce ;</li>
<li>sociétés de services ;</li>
<li>organisations non gouvernementales (ONGs) humanitaires de rang international.</li> </ul>
Camptocamp a ainsi développé une forte expertise dans les domaines suivants :
<ul><li>finance :<ul>
<li>localisation suisse, française et autrichienne ;</li>
<li>environnements multi-sociétés et multi-devises ;</li>
<li>rapports financiers (WebKit Reports) ;</li>
<li>automatisation bancaire : import de relevés bancaires, pré-remplissage des écritures comptables, lettrage de masse ;</li></ul></li>
<li>logistique :<ul>
<li>automatisation avec des douchettes et code-barres : scénarios de scan pour les réceptions, expéditions, mouvements internes, inventaires, fabrications... ;</li>
<li>problématiques spécifiques multi-stocks, traçabilité et synchronisations offline ;</li></ul></li>
<li>e-commerce :<ul>
<li>connecteur OpenERP Magento (bi-directionnel), permettant de synchroniser commandes, clients, produits, prix, méthodes de paiement et de livraison, expéditions... ; </li>
<li>connecteur OpenERP PrestaShop ;</li></ul></li>
<li>développement et mise en place d'applications métier 100 % spécifiques tirant parti de la puissance du framework d'OpenERP (OpenObject).</li></ul>
<br />
En outre, grâce à sa forte implication dans l'écosystème OpenERP depuis plusieurs années, Camptocamp a été promu par l’Éditeur OpenERP SA au statut de meilleur contributeur OpenERP en 2012 et 2013. <br/>
]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_26" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">3 gute Gründe, sich heute noch für Federal als Partner für die Implementierung Ihres ERP Projekts zu entscheiden: Sie haben erstens einen Software-Spezialisten, zweitens einen Hardware- und Performance-Fachmann UND drittens einen Betriebswirt mit Know-how im Projektmanagement. Und...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[3 gute Gründe, sich heute noch für Federal als Partner für die Implementierung Ihres ERP Projekts zu entscheiden: <br/>
Sie haben erstens einen Software-Spezialisten, zweitens einen Hardware- und Performance-Fachmann UND drittens einen Betriebswirt mit Know-how im Projektmanagement. Und was bedeutet das für Sie? Ganz einfach… <br/>
… Ihre ganz individuellen Anforderungen werden in der Standardsoftware abgebildet<br/>
… professionelle Konzeption des optimalen Sizings für Ihre Systemlandschaft<br/>
… Verständnis für kaufmännische und logistische Prozesse in Ihrem Unternehmen sowie Einbindung Ihrer Mitarbeiter und effizienter Einsatz von Ressourcen.<br/><br/>
Vor allem brauchen Sie einen zuverlässigen und professionellen Berater/Begleiter, der Ihnen zuhört, Ihre Herausforderungen ernst nimmt und sie in Ihrem Sinne umsetzt. Und das unter Einhaltung von Zeit- und Budgetvorgaben ohne Ihnen ein X für ein U vorzumachen. Willkommen bei Federal ]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_8" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">Wir bieten Implementierung, Anpassung und Schulung für OpenERP. Schon seit TinyERP 4 entwickeln wir auch kundenspezifische Module. Neben individuellen Lösungen gibt es bereits vorkonfigurierte Systeme für: - ...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[Wir bieten Implementierung, Anpassung und Schulung für OpenERP. Schon seit TinyERP 4 entwickeln wir auch kundenspezifische Module. Neben individuellen Lösungen gibt es bereits vorkonfigurierte Systeme für:<br/>
- Lebensmittelproduktion (z.B.: Frucht- und Gemüse) <br/>
- Serviceanbieter mit Projektmanagement <br/>
- Maschinenbau und Gerätehersteller]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_11" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">Luminous es una empresa tecnológica, dinámica, innovadora y ágil que desarrolla soluciones de Gestión Empresarial a través de su sistema propio de Inteligencia Artificial “NEUROVIP” NEUROVIP es un sistema que convie...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[<p style="padding-left:15px;">Luminous es una empresa tecnológica, dinámica, innovadora y ágil que desarrolla soluciones de Gestión Empresarial a través de su sistema propio de Inteligencia Artificial “NEUROVIP”. <br/> <br/>  NEUROVIP es un sistema que convierte los datos provenientes de las herramientas de Gestión Empresarial (ERP´s, CRM´s, DMS´s, BPM´s, etc.) en información relevante para la Toma de Decisiones Estratégicas de la Empresa.<br/> <br/>
 
Luminous con su sistema propio de Inteligencia Artificial “NEUROVIP” se dirige a todo tipo de organización, ya sea del sector público o privado.
 <br/> <br/>
Su utilidad radica en que se tomen decisiones estratégicas de forma oportuna y de manera eficiente para conseguir competitividad en las empresas frente a la globalización y su entorno.
 <br/> <br/>
NEUROVIP consta de tres fases:<br/>
1ª Fase: En la primera fase Analiza los datos definidos por el usuario.<br/>
2ª Fase: En la segunda fase Aprende alimentándose con información social y/o empresarial.<br/>
3ª Fase: En la tercera fase Recomienda priorizando intereses concretos de la empresa.</p>]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_7" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">Bank Wealthy and sons has developed expertise in all areas of OpenERP, working with clients to create accounting, invoicing, VAT, and reporting customisations to fulfil their business needs. Bank Wealthy and sons work closely with the OpenERP community to send changes upstream to further enhance OpenERP. Providing a full range...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[Bank Wealthy and sons has developed expertise in all areas of OpenERP, working with clients to create accounting, invoicing, VAT, and reporting customisations to fulfil their business needs. Bank Wealthy and sons work closely with the OpenERP community to send changes upstream to further enhance OpenERP. <br/><br/>

Providing a full range of free software services for the private and public sectors since 1998, Bank Wealthy and sons is now one of the largest independent open source consultancies, with Open Source Support Centres in the UK, Germany, the US and Canada. With a worldwide team of over 40 free software developers, including many active OpenERP contributors, Bank Wealthy and sons is Your One-Stop Shop for Open Source Support™.]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_21" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">Global Solutions helps organisations of all shapes and sizes gain a competitive advantage through Free and Open Source software. Our experienced team can provide strategic advice, implementation, integration with exis...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[Global Solutions helps organisations of all shapes and sizes gain a competitive advantage through Free and Open Source software. Our experienced team can provide strategic advice, implementation, integration with existing systems, hosting and support services for a wide range of open source applications. Working with our customers Global Solutions helps to select and deliver best-of-breed solutions using Open Source products. Key skills and partnerships include Ubuntu, vtiger CRM, OpenEMM, Alfresco and of course OpenERP.
 <br/> <br/>
Founded in 2006, our clients range from SMEs to globally recognised brands and public sector organisations.]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_15" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">Millennium Industries is a London based OpenERP partner.  Their specialist areas include accounting, CRM, manufacturing, stock, logistics, and supply chain management.  The company has completed over 15 projects with intric...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[Millennium Industries is a London based OpenERP partner.  Their specialist areas include accounting, CRM, manufacturing, stock, logistics, and supply chain management.  The company has completed over 15 projects with intricate consolidation and stock-accounting requirements for which they can provide references. <br/> <br/>
 
Millennium Industries have developed several accounting modules for OpenERP and are the leading experts in the UK for this area.  Additionally, a forefront success story of theirs is the nominal level data migrations from Sage Line 50 to OpenERP that allows unprecedented efficiency in system switchover. <br/> <br/>
 
Last but not least, Millennium Industries is the only UK partner with their own Europe-based fully staffed development centre, aimed to deliver to the exact client specification projects of any complexity. <br/> <br/>
Please contact Millennium Industries direct to discuss your business requirement and the company would be delighted to help.]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_10" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">The Jackson Group is an active and leading partner of OpenERP in the US. As OpenERP's longest active US partner, we help our clients leverage new methods, cost-effective tools and fresh technologies to simplify infrastructure, lower cost, and improve operations. Our goal is to help our clients become...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[The Jackson Group is an active and leading partner of OpenERP in the US.
As OpenERP's longest active US partner, we help our clients leverage new methods, cost-effective tools and fresh technologies to simplify infrastructure, lower cost, and improve operations.<br/> <br/>
Our goal is to help our clients become high-performing, competitive and profitable businesses.
We leverage robust model that combines:<br/>
<ul><li>
Implementations of feature rich, extensible, and cost-effective Open Source software (OpenERP) </li>
<li>Experienced consulting services </li>
<li>Domestic US, near-shore and offshore based resources </li>
<li>A highly-responsive support model </li>
<li>A strategy that drives US Localization and adds new capabilities to OpenERP </li>
</ul><br/><br/>
 
The Jackson Group’s OpenERP consulting services include: <br/>
<ul> <li>
Roadmap Development </li>
<li>Program/Project Management </li>
<li>Process Analysis </li>
<li>Implementation and Configuration (on-premise or on-demand environments) </li>
<li>Data Migration </li>
<li>Programming and Custom Module Development </li>
<li>Training</li>
<li>Support </li>
<li>Managed Services</li>]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_18" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">We are a technology consulting &amp; strategic advisory firm that creates value enhancing solutions through the use of advanced software for our clients worldwide. At Think Big Systems we bring operational experience combined...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[We are a technology consulting & strategic advisory firm that creates value enhancing solutions through the use of advanced software for our clients worldwide.
 <br/> <br/>
At Think Big Systems we bring operational experience combined with technological acumen. We understand that any software that supports business operations needs to be designed in such a way that facilitates the execution of critical operational processes, and serves as a tool to the users rather than a barrier. Our approach is focused on the process first, ensuring that it contributes to the goals of the company, we then optimize it, and design the software solutions to best support it.]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_9" model="res.partner">
        <field name="website_short_description">Best Designers is an IT services organization, established by 3 industry experts headquartered at Mumbai, India. The organization serve customers with Open Source Enterprise Software applications. We are specialized in...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[Best Designers is an IT services organization, established by 3 industry experts headquartered at Mumbai, India. The organization serve customers with Open Source Enterprise Software applications. We are specialized in <b>ERP Implementation, CRM Implementation, E-Commerce to ERP Integrations, Document Management Systems and Open Source Training.</b> Our key products include <b>OpenERP, Alfresco and Magento.</b> Our core objective is to deliver quality in <b>OpenERP Implementation Services</b> incorporating supreme value to enterprises globally, at an affordable price. Our experience in managing projects right from selecting tools and platforms to implement solutions has shown results in <b>Reducing IT Budgets for SME making Technology Affordable. </b>
 <br/> <br/>
Our ERP expertise is since 2005 and we mainly focus on OpenERP Implementation across the globe, being an <b>Off-shore Development Partner from India</b>, we are also associated with other OpenERP Partners across the globe to implement OpenERP Business Applications. In order to provide world class ERP, E–Commerce and Enterprise Solutions, we have designed innovative Implementation Methodologies and concepts, which help us provide reliable business solutions that meet present as well as future demands.
<br/><br/>
Best Designers has now emerged serving the Small and Medium Business – SMB’s with lots of Free and Open Source Software's, Our team is proficient to deliver quick and quality solutions. With a blend of experts with proven track record, our enterprise solution Business Consultants, ERP Consultants, Network Engineers, Software Developers, Web Architects, Software Testers and Search Engine Optimizers makes it possible to offer our clients affordable solutions that are both innovative and highly influential.
]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_24" model="res.partner">
        <field name="notification_email_send">none</field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_25" model="res.partner">
        <field name="notification_email_send">none</field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_26" model="res.partner">
        <field name="notification_email_send">none</field>
    </record>
    </data>
</openerp>
