<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<openerp>
    <!-- <data noupdate="1"> -->
    <data>

        <!-- TAGS -->
        <record id="blog_tag_1" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">functional</field>
        </record>
        <record id="blog_tag_2" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">technical</field>
        </record>
        <record id="blog_tag_3" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">website</field>
        </record>

        <!-- POSTS -->
        <record id="blog_post_1" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">The Future of Emails</field>
            <field name="sub_title">Ideas behing the OpenERP communication tools.</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_1"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_1')])]"/>
            <field name="website_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="website_meta_keywords">OpenERP, email</field>
            <field name="website_meta_description">The Future of Emails</field>
            <field name="content_image">/website_blog/static/src/img/post1.jpg</field>
            <field name="content"><![CDATA[
        <section class="mt16 mb16 readable" data-snippet-id='image-text'>
            <iframe width="361" height="200" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/EkbBFmIWoTE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
            <p>
                Emails are broken.
            </p><p>
                Emails make me waste my time. But I need them.
                Given the importance that emails have in our lives,
                it's incredible it's still one of the only software
                areas that did not evolve in the past 20 years!
            </p><p>
                Reading my inbox is the most unproductive task I do
                on a daily basis. I have to spend one full hour a
                day to process my emails. All the junk flows in the
                same inbox; spams, information that doesn't matter,
                quoted answers of quoted answers, etc. At the end
                of the hour, only 10 emails actually requested an
                answer from me. With a good tool, I could have done
                my job in 10 minutes!
            </p>
        </section>
        <section class="mt16 mb16 readable" data-snippet-id='text-image'>
            <p>
                At OpenERP, we build tools to bring productivity to
                enterprises. As emails and information flows are one of
                the biggest wastes of time in companies, we have to fix
                this.
            </p><p>
                To disrupt emails, you need more than just another user
                interface. We need to rethink the whole communication flow.
            </p>
            <h3>The Communication Mechanism of OpenERP</h3>
            <p>
                Here are the ideas behing the OpenERP communication tools:
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    Get Things Done: your inbox is a
                    todo list. You should be able to process (not only
                    read) the inbox and easily mark messages for future
                    actions. Every inbox should be empty after having
                    been processed; no more overload of information.
                    <img class="img-responsive" src="/website_blog/static/src/img/mail-sc-00.png"/>
                </li><li>
                    Keep control of what you want to receive or don't want
                    to receive. People should never receive spam. You
                    should follow/unfollow any kind of information in one
                    click.
                </li><li>
                    Productivity is key: our smart user
                    interface does not require you to click on every mail
                    to read a thread. Reading a full thread, replying,
                    attaching documents is super fast.
                    <img class="img-responsive" src="/website_blog/static/src/img/mail-sc-03.png"/>
                </li><li>
                    A mix of push & pull: Today, people
                    are victims of what others decide to push to them.
                    OpenERP differentiates:
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            Messages "for information":
                            you can pull them when you need some specific
                            information; they are not required to be read
                            every day.You receive only what you decided
                            to follow.This accounts for 90% of your daily
                            emails.Use the "Inbox" menu for these.
                        </li><li>
                            Messages "for action": they
                            require your immediate attention and you need
                            to process them all. This accounts for 10%
                            of your daily emails. Use the "To: me" menu
                            for these.
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </li><li>
                    Focus on the Content: Everything is
                    stripped to emphasize on the real message. No more
                    welcome introductions, greetings, signatures and legal
                    notes.We standardize the layout of each message.
                    (signatures are on the profile of a contact, not in
                    every message)
                </li><li>
                    Folders and mailing lists are great tools but too
                    complex in traditional email clients. In OpenERP, a
                    group of contacts that share a discussion can be
                    created with one click. Every group should have it's
                    own email address.
                </li>
            </ul>
            <p>All of this with a super sexy and minimalist user interface.</p>
        </section>
]]>
</field>
        </record>

        <record id="blog_post_2" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">Integrating your CMS and E-Commerce</field>
            <field name="sub_title">Building your company's website and selling your products online easy.</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_1"/>
            <field name="website_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_1')])]"/>
            <field name="content_image">/website_blog/static/src/img/post2.jpg</field>
            <field name="content">
<![CDATA[<section class="mt16 mb16 readable" data-snippet-id='image-text'>
            <div class="col-md-12">
                <img class="img-responsive" src="/website_blog/static/src/img/CMS_WMS_screens.jpg"/>
            </div>
            <div class="col-md-6 col-md-offset-3 mb16 mt16">
                <p class="text-center">
                    New Features Launched
                </p>
                <h4 class="text-center">
                    To add to an already comprehensive set of OpenERP
                    features, a website content management system (CMS
                    or WMS) has been developed and a beta release is
                    available from today, 31st January 2014.
                </h4>
            </div>
        </section>
        <section class="readable" data-snippet-id='text'>
            <p>
                OpenERP claims to be 'the Open Source software that makes
                building your company's website and selling your products
                online easy'. So how true is this statement?
            </p><p>
                "OpenERP's latest launch will allow a business to go from
                zero to trading online quicker than ever before,” Stuart
                Mackintosh, MD of Open Source specialist and OpenERP
                integration partner, OpusVL, explains. “The investment
                required to have a fully automated business system is
                dramatically reduced, enabling the small and medium
                enterprise to compete at a level of functionality and
                performance previously reserved for the big IT investors."
            </p>
            <h4>
                "Finally, the leading edge is being brought to the masses.
                It will now be the turn of the big players to catch up to
                the superior technologies of the SME."
            </h4>
            <p>
                "This is another clever and highly disruptive move by
                OpenERP,which will force other technology providers to
                take another look at the value they are providing to ensure
                that their 'solutions' can still compete."
            </p><p>
                "OpenERP now competes on many fronts, with no real
                competition out there to knock them off the top spot.
                With the launch of their integrated CMS and Ecommerce
                systems,it only elevates their position as one of the leading
                lights in the open source revolution. It will be at least 5
                years before another ERP or CMS provider will be able to
                compete at this level due to the technology currently
                employed by most industry providers."
            </p>
            <h4>Adding to industry leading technology</h4>
            <p>
                Like many modern website editors, with OpenERP you can edit
                content in-line, enabling you to see exactly what you are
                changing and ensure your changes suit the context.
            </p><p>
                However, unlike other web content management systems, it
                fully integrates into the back-end database. This means
                that when you edit a product description, image or price,
                it updates the product database in real time, providing a
                true self-service window into the business.
            </p><p>
                This provides a single source of data for your company and
                removes the need to create offline synchronisation between
                website and product database.
            </p><p>
                As it comes, there is a default website based on Bootstrap
                3, the latest industry standard for rapid development of
                multi-device websites backed by Twitter, so can be directly
                integrated with many web tools and works across all devices
                by default.
            </p>
            <h4>So, what does this mean to me and my business?</h4>
            <p>
                The CMS removes the need for Magento integration for the
                shopping basket and Drupal/Joomla for the website. For any
                organisation, this will reduce the technology footprint and
                eliminate the complexities of FTP or file transfer data
                uploads and exports which for many, are manual tasks.
                Implementation is easier and the web designer can get
                straight on with developing the site without requiring the
                project management and interactions with site developers,
                providing a quicker and more efficient deployment. However,
                for larger sites, stringent process and project management
                disciplines are still required to ensure a low-risk project.
            </p>
            <h4>How does it work in practice?</h4>
            <p>
                When items are placed in the basket, a sales order is
                created automatically to reflect the basket contents.
                Payments are recorded on the balance sheet and all
                accounting journal entries are automatic. As it is in real
                time, stock records are always accurate and decremented on
                the fly when orders placed.
            </p><p>
                Automatic translations can be created for international
                traders and available languages selected.
            </p>
            <p>
                Customer queries and returns can be set up to use the case
                handling system which will escalate depending on customer
                spend, grouping or profile and notify relevant parties as
                appropriate.
            </p><p>
                More information about the feature set can be found
                <a href="https://www.openerp.com/website_cms" target="_TOP">
                on the OpenERP website here</a>
            </p>
            <h4>Created in just four months</h4>
            <p>
                OpenERP competently manages customer and product data, and
                has mature sales work-flow built in, so the addition of the
                E-commerce module was achieved by presenting these
                components through a customer-friendly interface so most
                of the effort invested was creating the CMS functions. This
                was  achieved within just four months of development by a
                core team of 6 OpenERP developers and significant community
                support.
            </p><p>
                Inspiration has come from various other platforms including
                Prestashop, Magento and Drupal and contributors bring many
                years of industry experience across many platforms.
            </p>
        </section>


]]>
</field>
        </record>
        <record id="blog_post_3" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">Sorry SAP Campaign - The Making Of</field>
            <field name="sub_title">To lead the enterprise management market with a fully open source software.</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_1"/>
            <field name="website_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="website_meta_keywords">OpenERP, News, Sorry SAP</field>
            <field name="website_meta_description">Sorry SAP Campaign - The Making Of</field>
            <field name="content_image">/website_blog/static/src/img/post3.jpg</field>
            <field name="content"><![CDATA[
        <section class="readable" data-snippet-id="text">
            <p>I needed to change the world. I wanted to ... You know how
            it is when you are young; you have big dreams, a lot of energ
            and naïve stupidity. My dream was to lead the enterprise
            management market with a fully open source software.(I also
            wanted to get 100 employees before 30 years old with a
            self-financed company but I failed this one by a few months).
            </p>
        </section>
        <section class="readable" data-snippet-id="text-image">
            <p>
                To fuel my motivation, I had to pick someone to fight
                against. In business, it's like a playground. When you
                arrive in a new school, if you want to quickly become the
                leader, you must choose the class bully, the older guy who
                terrorises small boys,and kick his butt in front of
                everyone. That was my strategy with SAP, the enterprise
                software giant.
            </p><p>
                So, in 2005, I started to develop the TinyERP product, the
                software that (at least in my mind) would change the enterprise
                world. While preparing for the "day of the fight" in 2006,
                I <a href="http://whois.domaintools.com/sorrysap.com">
                bought the SorrySAP.com </a>domain name. I put it on hold
                for 6 years, waiting for the right moment to use it.
                I thought it would take 3 years to deprecate a 77 billion
                dollars company just because open source is so cool.
                Sometimes it's better for your self-motivation not to
                face reality...
            </p><p>
                To make things happen, I worked hard, very hard. I worked
                13 hours a day, 7 days a week, with no vacations for 7
                years.I lost friendships and broke up with my girlfriend in
                the process (fortunately, I found a more valuable wife
                now. I will explain later why she is worth 1 million EUR
                :).
            </p><p>
                Three years later, I discovered you can't change the world
                if you are "tiny". Especially if the United States is part
                of this world, where it's better to be a BigERP, rather
                than a TinyERP. Can you imagine how small you feel
                <a href="http://www.slideshare.net/openobject/danone-deployes-openerp-locally">
                in front of Danone's directors</a> asking; "but why
                should we pay millions of dollars for a tiny software?"
                So, we renamed TinyERP to OpenERP.
            </p><p>
                As we worked hard, things started to evolve. We were
                developing dozens of modules for OpenERP, the open source
                community was growing and I was even able to pay all
                employees' salaries at the end of the month without fear
                (which was a situation I struggled with for 4 years).
            </p><p>
                In 2010, we had a 100+ employees company selling services
                on OpenERP and a powerful but ugly product. This is what
                happens when delivering services to customers distracts
                you from building an exceptional product.
            </p><p>
                It was time to do a pivot in the business model.
            </p>
            <h3>The Pivot</h3>
            <p>
                We wanted to switch from a service company to a software
                publisher company. This would allow to increase our efforts
                in our research and development activities. As a result,
                we <a href="http://v6.openerp.com/node/465">changed our
                business model</a> and decided to stop our services to
                customers and focus on building a strong partner network
                and maintenance offer. This would cost money, so I had to
                raise a few million euros.
            </p><p>
                After a few months of pitching investors, I got roughly
                10 LOI from different VCs. We chosed Sofinnova Partners,
                the biggest European VC, and Xavier Niel the founder of
                Iliad, the only company in France funded in the past 10
                years to have reached the 1 billion euro valuation.
            </p><p>
                I signed the LOI. I didn't realize that this contract could
                have turned me into a homeless person. (I already had a dog,
                all I needed was to lose a lot of money to become homeless).
                The fund raising was based on a company valuation but there
                was a financial mechanism to re-evaluate the company up by
                9.8 m€ depending on the turnover of the next 4 years. I should
                have received warrants convertible into shares if we achieved
                the turnover targeted in the business plan.
            </p><p>
                The night before receiving the warrants in front of the
                notary, my wife checked the contracts. She asked me what
                would be the taxation on these warrants. I rang the lawyer
                and guess what? Belgium is probably the only country in
                the world where you have to pay taxes on warrants when you
                receive them, even if you never reach the conditions to
                convert them into shares.If I had accepted these warrants,
                I would have had to pay a 12.5% tax on 9.8 m€; resulting
                in a tax of 1.2m€ to pay in 18 months! So, my wife is worth
                1.2 million EUR. I would have ended up a homeless person
                without her, as I still did not have a salary at that time.
            </p><p>
                We changed the deal and I got the 3 million EUR. It allowed
                me to recruit a rocking management team.
            </p>
            <img class="img-responsive" src="/website_blog/static/src/img/OpemERP_board.jpg"/>
            <h3 class="mt16">Being a mature company<h3>
            <p>
                With this money in our bank account, we boosted two
                departments: R&D and Sales. We burned two million EUR in
                18 months,mostly in salaries. The company started to grow
                even faster.We developed a partner network of 500 partners
                in 100 countries and we started to sign contracts with 6
                zeros.
            </p><p>
                Then, things became different. You know, tedious things like
                handling human resources, board meetings, dealing with big
                customer contracts, traveling to launch international
                subsidiaries. We did boring stuff like budgets, career paths,
                management meetings, etc.
            </p><p>
                2011 was a complex year. We did not meet our expectations:
                we only achieved 70% of the forecasted sales budget. Our
                management meetings were tense. We under performed. We were not
                satisfied with ourselves. We had a constant feeling that we
                missed something. It's a strange feeling to build extraordinary
                things but to not be proud of ourselves.
            </p><p>
                But one day, someone (I don't remember who, I have a
                goldfish memory) made a graph of the monthly turnover
                of the past 2 years. It was like waking up from a nighmare.
                In fact,it was not that bad, we had multiplied by 10 the
                monthly turnover over the span of roughly two years!
                This is when we understood that OpenERP is a marathon,
                not a sprint. Only 100% growth a year is ok... if you can
                keep the rhythm for several years.
            </p>
            <img class="img-responsive" src="/website_blog/static/src/img/turnover_updated.png"/>
            <p class="text-center" section_inner="1">
                OpenERP Monthly Turnover
            </p><p>
                As usual, I should have listened to my wife. She is way
                more lucid than I am. Every week I complained to her "it's
                not good enough, we should grow faster, what am I missing?"
                and she used to reply; "But you already are the
                <a href="http://v6.openerp.com/node/1244/2012/10">
                fastest growing company in Belgium!". </a>(Deloitte awarded
                us as the fastest growing company of Belgium with 1549%
                growth of the turnover between 2007 and 2011)
            </p>
            <h3 class="mt16">Changing the world</h3>
            <p>
                Then, the dream started to become reality. We started to
                get clues that what we did would change the world:
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    With 1.000 installations per day, we became the most
                    installed management software in the world,
                </li><li>
                    <a href="http://www.amazon.com/OpenERP-Evaluation-SAP-as-Reference/dp/296008764X/ref=sr_1_3?ie=UTF8&qid=1351150366&sr=8-3&keywords=openerp">
                        Analysts from Big 4 started to prefer OpenERP over SAP,
                    </a>
                </li><li>
                    OpenERP is now a <a href="http://www.nathan.fr/catalogue/catalogue_detail_enseignants.asp?ean13=9782091619262">
                    compulsory subject for the baccalaureate in France</a>
                    like Word, Excel and Powerpoint
                </li><li>
                    60 new modules are released every month (we became
                    the wikipedia of the management software thanks to
                    our strong community)
                </li>
            </ul>
            <p>
                Something is happening... And it's big!
            </p><p>
                OpenERP 7.0 is about to be released and I know you will be
                astonished by it.
            </p><p>
                The official release is planned for the 21th of December.
                As the Mayas predicted it, this is the end of an age,
                the old ERP dinosaurs.
            </p><p>
                It's time to pull out the Ace: the SorrySAP.com domain
                name that I bought 6 years ago.
            </p><p>
                If you want to test the v7 version online, just go
                <a href="https://www.openerp.com/"> the homepage.</a>
            </p>
        </section>
 ]]>
</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</openerp>
