<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="blog_blog_1" model="blog.blog">
            <field name="name">Travel</field>
            <field name="subtitle">Holiday tips</field>
            <field name="cover_properties">{"background-image": "url('/website_blog/static/src/img/blog_1.jpeg')", "text_size_class": "o_record_cover_font_big", "resize_class": "o_record_has_cover cover_mid", "background-color": "oe_black", "opacity": "0.4"}</field>
        </record>
        <record id="blog_blog_2" model="blog.blog">
            <field name="name">Astronomy</field>
            <field name="subtitle">Astronomy is “stargazing"</field>
            <field name="cover_properties">{"background-image": "url('/website_blog/static/src/img/blog_2.jpeg')", "text_size_class": "o_record_cover_font_big", "resize_class": "o_record_has_cover cover_mid", "background-color": "oe_black", "opacity": "0.4"}</field>
        </record>

        <!-- TAGS -->
        <record id="blog_tag_1" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">hotels</field>
        </record>
        <record id="blog_tag_2" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">adventure</field>
        </record>
        <record id="blog_tag_3" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">guides</field>
        </record>
        <record id="blog_tag_4" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">telescopes</field>
        </record>
        <record id="blog_tag_5" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">discovery</field>
        </record>

        <!-- POSTS -->
        <record id="blog_post_1" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">Sierra Tarahumara</field>
            <field name="subtitle">An exciting mix of relaxation, culture, history, wildlife and hiking.</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_1"/>
            <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="published_date" eval="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_1'), ref('blog_tag_2')])]"/>
            <field name="cover_properties">{"background-image": "url('/website_blog/static/src/img/cover_1.jpg')", "resize_class": "o_record_has_cover cover_full", "text_size_class": "o_record_cover_font_big", "background-color": "oe_black", "opacity": "0"}</field>
            <field name="content"><![CDATA[
<p class="lead">Sierra Tarahumara, popularly known as Copper Canyon is situated in Mexico. The area is a favorite destination among those seeking an adventurous vacation.</p>
<p>Copper Canyon is one of the six gorges in the area. Although the name suggests that the gorge might have some relevance to copper mining, this is not the case. The name is derived from the copper and green lichen covering the canyon. Copper Canyon has two climatic zones. The region features an alpine climate at the top and a subtropical climate at the lower levels. Winters are cold with frequent snowstorms at the higher altitudes. Summers are dry and hot. The capital city, Chihuahua, is a high altitude desert where weather ranges from cold winters to hot summers. The region is unique because of the various ecosystems that exist within it.</p>

<p>Another unique feature of Copper Canyon is the presence of the Tarahumara Indian culture. These semi-nomadic people live in cave dwellings. Their livelihood chiefly depends on farming and cattle ranching.</p>
<figure class="mt-2 mb-4">
    <img src="/website_blog/static/src/img/content_1_1.jpg" class="img-fluid w-100"/>
    <figcaption class="figure-caption">Photo by PoloX Hernandez, @elpolox</figcaption>
</figure>

<blockquote class="blockquote my-5">
    <em class="h4 my-0">Apart from the native population, the local wildlife is also a major crowd puller.</em>
    <footer class="blockquote-footer">Someone famous in <cite title="Source Title">Source Title</cite></footer>
</blockquote>

<p>Several migratory and native birds, mammals and reptiles call Copper Canyon their home. The exquisite fauna in this near-pristine land is also worth checking out.</p>
<figure class="mt-2 mb-4">
    <img src="/website_blog/static/src/img/content_1_2.jpg" class="img-fluid w-100"/>
    <figcaption class="figure-caption">Photo by Boris Smokrovic, @borisworkshop</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>A traveler may choose to explore the area by hiking around the canyon or venturing into it. Detailed planning is required for those who wish to venture into the depths of the canyon. There are a number of travel companies that specialize in organizing tours to the region. Visitors can fly to Copper Canyon using a tourist visa, which is valid for 180 days. Travelers can also drive from anywhere in the United States and acquire a visa at the Mexican customs station at the border.</p>
<p>A holiday to the Copper Canyon promises to be an exciting mix of relaxation, culture, history, wildlife and hiking.</p>
]]>
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="blog_post_2" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">Maui helicopter tours</field>
            <field name="subtitle">A great way to discover hidden places</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_1"/>
            <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="published_date" eval="(datetime.now()-relativedelta(days=2)).strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_2')])]"/>
            <field name="cover_properties">{"background-image": "url('/website_blog/static/src/img/cover_2.jpg')", "resize_class": "o_record_has_cover cover_mid", "text_size_class": "o_record_cover_font_big", "background-color": "oe_blue", "opacity": "0.4"}</field>
            <field name="content"><![CDATA[
<section class="container">
    <div class="row">
        <div class="col">
            <p class="lead">Maui helicopter tours are a great way to see the island from a different perspective and have a fun adventure. If you have never been on a helicopter before, this is a great place to do it.</p>
            <p>You will see all the beauty that Maui has to offer and can have a great time for the entire family. Tours are not too expensive and last from forty five minutes to over an hour. You can see places that are typically inaccessible with Maui helicopter tours. Places that are not available by foot or vehicle can be seen by air. Breathtaking sights await those who are up for some fun Maui helicopter tours. If you will be staying on the island for a considerable amount of time, you may want to think about doing multiple Maui helicopter tours.</p>
        </div>
        <div class="col-12 col-md-auto">
            <figure>
                <img src="/website_blog/static/src/img/content_2_1.jpg" class="img-fluid" style="max-height:450px"/>
                <figcaption class="figure-caption">Photo by Jon Ly, @jonatron</figcaption>
            </figure>
        </div>
    </div>
</section>

<h2 class="mt-5">East Maui</h2>
<figure class="mt-2 mb-4">
    <img src="/website_blog/static/src/img/content_2_2.jpg" class="img-fluid w-100"/>
    <figcaption class="figure-caption">Photo by Anton Repponen, @repponen</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>East Maui helicopter tours will give you a view of the ten thousand foot volcano, Haleakala or House of the sun. This volcano is dormant and last erupted in 1790. You will be able to see the crater of the volcano and the dry, arid earth surrounding the south side of the volcano’s slop with Maui helicopter tours.</p>
<p>The view of this is truly breathtaking and is a sight not to be missed. It is also highly educational with a chance to see a dormant volcano up close, something that can not be seen every day. On the northern and southern sides of the volcano, you will see an incredible different view however. These sides are lush and green and you will be able to see some beautiful waterfalls and gorgeous brush. Tropical rainforests abound on this side of the island and it is something that is not easily accessible by any other means than by air.</p>
<p>Maui helicopter tours will allow you to see all of these sights. Make sure to take a camera or video with you when going on Maui helicopter tours to capture the beauty of the scenery and to show friends and family at home all the wonderful things you saw while on vacation.</p>

<h2 class="mt-5">Molokai Maui </h2>
<figure class="mt-2 mb-4">
    <img src="/website_blog/static/src/img/content_2_3.jpg" class="img-fluid w-100"/>
    <figcaption class="figure-caption">Photo by Denys Nevozhai, @dnevozhai</figcaption>
</figure>
<p>Molokai Maui helicopter tours will take you to a different island but one that is only nine miles away and easily accessible by air. This island has a very small population with a different culture and scenery. The entire coast of the northeast is lined with cliffs and remote beaches. They are completely inaccessible by any other means of transportation than air.
People who live on the island have never even seen this remarkable scenery unless they have taken Maui helicopter tours to view it. When the weather has been rainy and there is a lot of rainfall for he season you will see many astounding waterfalls.</p>
<p>The cliffs in this region are among the highest in the world and to see water cascading from the high peaks is simply breathtaking. The short jaunt from Maui with Maui helicopter tours is well worth seeing the beauty of this natural environment.</p>
<p>Maui helicopter tours are a great way to tour those places that can not be reached on foot or by car. The tours last approximately one hour and range from approximately one hundred eight five dollars to two hundred forty dollars person. For many, this is a once in a lifetime opportunity to see natural scenery that will not be available again. Taking cameras and videos to capture the moments will also allow you to relive the tour again and again as you reminisce throughout the years.</p>
]]>
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="blog_post_3" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">How to choose the right hotel</field>
            <field name="subtitle">Facts you should bear in mind.</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_1"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_1')])]"/>
            <field name="website_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="published_date" eval="(datetime.now()-relativedelta(days=1)).strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
            <field name="cover_properties">{"background-image": "url('/website_blog/static/src/img/cover_3.jpg')", "resize_class": "o_record_has_cover cover_mid", "background-color": "oe_black", "opacity": "0.4"}</field>
            <field name="content"><![CDATA[
<p class="lead">So you’re going abroad, you’ve chosen your destination and now you have to choose a hotel.</p>
<p>Ten years ago, you’d have probably visited your local travel agent and trusted the face-to-face advice you were given by the so called ‘experts’. The 21st Century way to select and book your hotel is of course on the Internet, by using travel websites.</p>

<p>But how do you sift through the amazing choices on offer? And more importantly, do you really trust the photographs and descriptions of the hotels that they have awarded themselves with the motivation of getting bookings? Traveler reviews can be helpful, but you need to exercise caution. They are often biased, sometimes out of date, and may not serve your interests at all. How do you know that the features that are important to the reviewer are important to you?</p>

<blockquote>
    <em class="h4 my-0">The more reviews you read, the more you notice how they tend to cluster at the extremes of opinion.</em>
    <footer class="blockquote-footer">Someone famous in <cite title="Source Title">Source Title</cite></footer>
</blockquote>

<figure class="mt-2 mb-4">
    <img src="/website_blog/static/src/img/content_3_1.jpg" class="img-fluid w-100"/>
    <figcaption class="figure-caption">Photo by Jason Briscoe, @jbriscoe</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Then there’s the problem of the reviewer’s motivation. The more reviews you read, the more you notice how they tend to cluster at the extremes of opinion. On one end, you have angry reviewers with axes to grind; at the other, you have delighted guests who lavish praise beyond belief. You’ll not be surprised to learn that hotels sometimes post their own glowing reviews, or that competitor’s line up for the chance to lambaste the competition with bad reviews. It makes sense to consider what is really important to you when selecting a hotel. You should then choose an online hotel directory that gives up-to-date, independent, impartial information that really matters.
</p>

<h4 class="mt-4">Here are some of the key facts you should bear in mind:</h4>
<ol>
    <li class="mb-3"><h5>Location</h5>
    If it matters that your hotel is, for example, on the beach, close to the theme park, or convenient for the airport, then location is paramount. Any decent directory should offer a location map of the hotel and its surroundings. There should be distance charts to the airport offered as well as some form of interactive map.</li>
    <li class="mb-3"><h5>Style</h5>
    It is important to choose a hotel that makes you feel comfortable – contemporary or traditional furnishings, local decor or international, formal or relaxed. The ideal hotel directory should let you know of the options available.</li>
    <li class="mb-3"><h5>Restaurants, Cafes and Bars</h5>
    Local color is great but the hotel’s own restaurants and bars can play an important part in your stay. You should be aware of choice, style and whether or not they are smart or informal. A good hotel report should tell you this, and particularly about breakfast facilities.</li>
    <li class="mb-3"><h5>Bedroom Facilities</h5>
    You should always carefully consider the type of facilities you need from your bedroom and find the hotel that has those you consider important. The hotel directory website should elaborate on matters such as: bed size, Internet Access (its cost, whether there is WIFI or wired broadband connection), Complimentary amenities, views from the room and luxury offerings like a Pillow menu or Bath menu, choice of smoking or non smoking rooms etc.</li>
</ol>
<p>These things really do matter and any decent hotel directory should give you this sort of advice on bedrooms – not just the number of rooms which is the usual option!</p>
<ol>
    <li class="mb-3"><h5>Children’s’ Facilities</h5>
    More important to the family traveler than the business traveler, you should find out just how child friendly the hotel is from the directory and make your decision from there. One thing worth looking for is whether the hotel offers a baby sitters service. For the business traveler wishing to escape children this is of course very relevant too – perhaps a hotel that is not child friendly would be something more appropriate!</li>
    <li class="mb-3"> <h5>Leisure Facilities</h5>
    The site should offer a detailed analysis of leisure services within the hotel – spa, pool, gym, sauna – as well as details of any other facilities nearby such as golf courses. 7. Special Needs: the hotel directory site should advise the visitor of each hotel’s special needs services and accessibility policy. Whilst again this does not apply to every visitor, it is absolutely vital to some.</li>
</ol>

<p>Finally and most importantly, the quality hotel directory inspection team should have visited the hotel in question on a regular basis, met the staff, slept in a bedroom and tried the food. They should experience the hotel as only a hotel guest can and it is only then that they are really in a strong position to write about the hotel.</p>
]]>
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="blog_post_4" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">How To Look Up</field>
            <field name="subtitle">Be aware of this thing called “astronomy”</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_2"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_5')])]"/>
            <field name="website_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="published_date" eval="(datetime.now()-relativedelta(days=6)).strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
            <field name="cover_properties">{"background-image": "url('/website_blog/static/src/img/cover_4.jpg')", "resize_class": "o_record_has_cover cover_mid", "text_size_class": "o_record_cover_font_big", "text_align_class": "text-center", "background-color": "oe_black", "opacity": "0.2"}</field>
            <field name="content"><![CDATA[
<p class="lead">It is safe to say that at some point on our lives, each and every one of us has that moment when we are suddenly stunned when we come face to face with the enormity of the universe that we see in the night sky.</p>

<p>For many of us who are city dwellers, we don’t really notice that sky up there on a routine basis. The lights of the city do a good job of disguising the amazing display that is above all of our heads all of the time.</p>

<blockquote class="blockquote my-5">
    <em class="h4 my-0">That “Wow” moment is what astrology is all about.</em>
    <footer class="blockquote-footer">Someone famous in <cite title="Source Title">Source Title</cite></footer>
</blockquote>

<p>So it might be that once a year vacation to a camping spot or a trip to a relative’s house out in the country that we find ourselves outside when the spender of the night sky suddenly decides to put on it’s spectacular show. If you have had that kind of moment when you were literally struck breathless by the spender the night sky can show to us, you can probably remember that exact moment when you could say little else but “wow” at what you saw.</p>

<figure class="mt-2 mb-4">
    <img src="/website_blog/static/src/img/content_4_1.jpg" class="img-fluid w-100"/>
    <figcaption class="figure-caption">Photo by Arto Marttinen, @wandervisions</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>That “Wow” moment is what astrology is all about. For some, that wow moment becomes a passion that leads to a career studying the stars. For a lucky few, that wow moment because an all consuming obsession that leads to them traveling to the stars in the space shuttle or on one of our early space missions. But for most of us astrology may become a pastime or a regular hobby. But we carry that wow moment with us for the rest of our lives and begin looking for ways to look deeper and learn more about the spectacular universe we see in the millions of stars above us each night.</p>

<h4>Get started</h4>
<p>To get started in learning how to observe the stars much better, there are some basic things we might need to look deeper, beyond just what we can see with the naked eye and begin to study the stars as well as enjoy them. The first thing you need isn’t equipment at all but literature. A good star map will show you the major constellations, the location of the key stars we use to navigate the sky and the planets that will appear larger than stars. And if you add to that map some well done introductory materials into the hobby of astronomy, you are well on your way.</p>

<h4>Get a telescope</h4>
<p>The next thing we naturally want to get is a good telescope. You may have seen a hobbyist who is well along in their study setting up those really cool looking telescopes on a hill somewhere. That excites the amateur astronomer in you because that must be the logical next step in the growth of your hobby. But how to buy a good telescope can be downright confusing and intimidating.</p>

<p>Before you go to that big expense, it might be a better next step from the naked eye to invest in a good set of binoculars. There are even binoculars that are suited for star gazing that will do just as good a job at giving you that extra vision you want to see just a little better the wonders of the universe. A well designed set of binoculars also gives you much more mobility and ability to keep your “enhanced vision” at your fingertips when that amazing view just presents itself to you.</p>

<p>None of this precludes you from moving forward with your plans to put together an awesome telescope system. Just be sure you get quality advice and training on how to configure your telescope to meet your needs. Using these guidelines, you will enjoy hours of enjoyment stargazing at the phenomenal sights in the night sky that are beyond the naked eye.</p>
]]>
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="blog_post_5" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">What If They Let You Run The Hubble</field>
            <field name="subtitle">The beauty of astronomy is that anybody can do it.</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_2"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_4'), ref('blog_tag_5')])]"/>
            <field name="website_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="published_date" eval="(datetime.now()-relativedelta(days=4)).strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
            <field name="cover_properties">{"background-image": "url('/website_blog/static/src/img/cover_5.jpg')", "resize_class": "o_record_has_cover cover_mid", "text_align_class": "text-center", "background-color": "oe_black", "opacity": "0.2"}</field>
            <field name="content"><![CDATA[
<p class="lead">From the tiniest baby to the most advanced astrophysicist, there is something for anyone who wants to enjoy astronomy. In fact, it is a science that is so accessible that virtually anybody can do it virtually anywhere they are. All they have to know how to do is to look up.</p>
<p>It really is amazing when you think about it that just by looking up on any given night, you could see virtually hundreds of thousands of stars, star systems, planets, moons, asteroids, comets and maybe a even an occasional space shuttle might wander by. It is even more breathtaking when you realize that the sky you are looking up at is for all intents and purposes the exact same sky that our ancestors hundreds and thousands of years ago enjoyed when they just looked up.</p>

<blockquote class="blockquote my-5">
    <em class="h4 my-0">There is something timeless about the cosmos.</em>
    <footer class="blockquote-footer">Someone famous in <cite title="Source Title">Source Title</cite></footer>
</blockquote>

<p>There is something timeless about the cosmos. The fact that the planets and the moon and the stars beyond them have been there for ages does something to our sense of our place in the universe. In fact, many of the stars we “see” with our naked eye are actually light that came from that star hundreds of thousands of years ago. That light is just now reaching the earth. So in a very real way, looking up is like time travel.</p>

<figure class="mt-2 mb-4">
    <img src="/website_blog/static/src/img/content_5_1.jpg" class="img-fluid w-100"/>
    <figcaption class="figure-caption">Photo by SpaceX, @spacex</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>While anyone can look up and fall in love with the stars at any time, the fun of astronomy is learning how to become more and more skilled and equipped in star gazing that you see and understand more and more each time you look up. Here are some steps you can take to make the moments you can devote to your hobby of astronomy much more enjoyable.</p>

<h4>Get some history</h4>
<p>Learning the background to the great discoveries in astronomy will make your moments star gazing more meaningful. It is one of the oldest sciences on earth so find out the greats of history who have looked at these stars before you.</p>

<h4>Know what you are looking at</h4>
<p>It is great fun to start learning the constellations, how to navigate the night sky and find the planets and the famous stars. There are web sites and books galore to guide you.</p>

<h4>Get a geek</h4>
<p>Astronomy clubs are lively places full of knowledgeable amateurs who love to share their knowledge with you. For the price of a coke and snacks, they will go star gazing with you and overwhelm you with trivia and great knowledge.</p>

<h4>Know when to look</h4>
<p> Not only knowing the weather will make sure your star gazing is rewarding but if you learn when the big meteor showers and other big astronomy events will happen will make the excitement of astronomy come alive for you.</p>

<p>And when all is said and done,<b> get equipped</b>. Your quest for newer and better telescopes will be a lifelong one. Let yourself get addicted to astronomy and the experience will enrich every aspect of life. It will be an addiction you never want to break.</p>
]]>
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="blog_post_6" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">Buying A Telescope</field>
            <field name="subtitle">Before you make your first purchase…</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_2"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_3'), ref('blog_tag_4')])]"/>
            <field name="website_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="published_date" eval="(datetime.now()-relativedelta(days=3)).strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
            <field name="cover_properties">{"background-image": "url('/website_blog/static/src/img/cover_6.jpg')", "resize_class": "o_record_has_cover cover_full", "text_size_class": "o_record_cover_font_huge", "text_align_class": "text-center", "background-color": "oe_black", "opacity": "0.2"}</field>
            <field name="content"><![CDATA[
<p class="lead">Buying the right telescope to take your love of astronomy to the next level is a big next step in the development of your passion for the stars.</p>
<p>In many ways, it is a big step from someone who is just fooling around with astronomy to a serious student of the science. But you and I both know that there is still another big step after buying a telescope before you really know how to use it.</p>
<p>So it is critically important that you get just the right telescope for where you are and what your star gazing preferences are. To start with, let’s discuss the three major kinds of telescopes and then lay down some “Telescope 101″ concepts to increase your chances that you will buy the right thing.</p>

<blockquote class="blockquote my-5">
    <em class="h4 my-0">It is critically important that you get just the right telescope.</em>
    <footer class="blockquote-footer">Someone famous in <cite title="Source Title">Source Title</cite></footer>
</blockquote>

<p>So to select just the right kind of telescope, your objectives in using the telescope are important. To really understand the strengths and weaknesses not only of the lenses and telescope design but also in how the telescope performs in various star gazing situations, it is best to do some homework up front and get exposure to the different kinds. So before you make your first purchase…</p>
<ul>
    <li>Above all, <b>establish a relationship with a reputable telescope shop</b> that employs people who know their stuff. If you buy your telescope at a Wal-Mart or department store, the odds you will get the right thing are remote.</li>
    <li><b>Pick the brains of the experts</b>. If you are not already active in an astronomy society or club, the sales people at the telescope store will be able to guide you to the active societies in your area. Once you have connections with people who have bought telescopes, you can get advice about what works and what to avoid that is more valid than anything you will get from a web article or a salesperson at Wal-Mart.</li>
    <li><b>Try before you buy.</b> This is another advantage of going on some field trips with the astronomy club. You can set aside some quality hours with people who know telescopes and have their rigs set up to examine their equipment, learn the key technical aspects, and try them out before you sink money in your own set up.</li>
    <li><b>Binoculars are lightweight and portable.</b> Unless you have the luxury to set up and operate an observatory from your deck, you are probably going to travel to perform your viewings. Binoculars go with you much easier and they are more lightweight to carry to the country and use while you are there than a cumbersome telescope set up kit.</li>
</ul>

<figure class="mt-2 mb-4">
    <img src="/website_blog/static/src/img/content_6_1.jpg" class="img-fluid w-100"/>
    <figcaption class="figure-caption">Photo by Teddy Kelley, @teddykelley</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>There are other considerations to factor into your final purchase decision.</p>

<h4>How mobile must your telescope be?</h4>
<p>The tripod or other accessory decisions will change significantly with a telescope that will live on your deck versus one that you plan to take to many remote locations.</p>
<h4>Along those lines, how difficult is the set up and break down?</h4>
<p>How complex is the telescope and will you have trouble with maintenance? Network to get the answers to these and other questions. If you do your homework like this, you will find just the right telescope for this next big step in the evolution of your passion for astronomy.</p>
]]>
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="blog_post_7" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">Beyond The Eye</field>
            <field name="subtitle">Becoming part of the society of devoted amateur astronomers.</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_2"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_5')])]"/>
            <field name="website_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="published_date" eval="(datetime.now()-relativedelta(days=7)).strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
            <field name="cover_properties">{"background-image": "url('/website_blog/static/src/img/cover_7.jpg')", "resize_class": "o_record_has_cover cover_mid", "text_size_class": "o_record_cover_font_big", "background-color": "oe_black", "opacity": "0.4"}</field>
            <field name="content"><![CDATA[
<p class="lead">For many of us, our very first experience of learning about the celestial bodies begins when we saw our first full moon in the sky. It is truly a magnificent view even to the naked eye.</p>
<p>If the night is clear, you can see amazing detail of the lunar surface just star gazing on in your back yard.
Naturally, as you grow in your love of astronomy, you will find many celestial bodies fascinating. But the moon may always be our first love because is the one far away space object that has the unique distinction of flying close to the earth and upon which man has walked.</p>

<blockquote class="blockquote my-5">
    <em class="h4 my-0">Your study of the moon, like anything else, can go from the simple to the very complex.</em>
    <footer class="blockquote-footer">Someone famous in <cite title="Source Title">Source Title</cite></footer>
</blockquote>

<p>To gaze at the moon with the naked eye, making yourself familiar with the lunar map will help you pick out the seas, craters and other geographic phenomenon that others have already mapped to make your study more enjoyable. Moon maps can be had from any astronomy shop or online and they are well worth the investment.</p>

<h2>The best time to view the moon.</h2>
<p>The best time to view the moon, obviously, is at night when there are few clouds and the weather is accommodating for a long and lasting study. The first quarter yields the greatest detail of study. And don’t be fooled but the blotting out of part of the moon when it is not in full moon stage. The phenomenon known as “earthshine” gives you the ability to see the darkened part of the moon with some detail as well, even if the moon is only at quarter or half display.</p>

<figure class="mt-2 mb-4">
    <img src="/website_blog/static/src/img/content_7_1.jpg" class="img-fluid w-100"/>
    <figcaption class="figure-caption">Photo by Patrick Brinksma, @patrickbrinksma</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>To kick it up a notch, a good pair of binoculars can do wonders for the detail you will see on the lunar surface. For best results, get a good wide field in the binocular settings so you can take in the lunar landscape in all its beauty. And because it is almost impossible to hold the binoculars still for the length of time you will want to gaze at this magnificent body in space, you may want to add to your equipment arsenal a good tripod that you can affix the binoculars to so you can study the moon in comfort and with a stable viewing platform.</p>
<p>Of course, to take your moon worship to the ultimate, stepping your equipment up to a good starter telescope will give you the most stunning detail of the lunar surface. With each of these upgrades your knowledge and the depth and scope of what you will be able to see will improve geometrically. For many amateur astronomers, we sometimes cannot get enough of what we can see on this our closest space object. </p>

<figure class="mt-2 mb-4">
    <img src="/website_blog/static/src/img/content_7_2.jpg" class="img-fluid w-100"/>
    <figcaption class="figure-caption">Photo by Greg Rakozy, @grakozy</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>To take it to a natural next level, you may want to take advantage of partnerships with other astronomers or by visiting one of the truly great telescopes that have been set up by professionals who have invested in better techniques for eliminating atmospheric interference to see the moon even better. The internet can give you access to the Hubble and many of the huge telescopes that are pointed at the moon all the time. Further, many astronomy clubs are working on ways to combine multiple telescopes, carefully synchronized with computers for the best view of the lunar landscape.</p>

<p>Becoming part of the society of devoted amateur astronomers will give you access to these organized efforts to reach new levels in our ability to study the Earth’s moon. And it will give you peers and friends who share your passion for astronomy and who can share their experience and areas of expertise as you seek to find where you might look next in the huge night sky, at the moon and beyond it in your quest for knowledge about the seemingly endless universe above us. </p>
]]>
            </field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>
