<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <!-- TAGS -->
        <record id="blog_tag_1" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">functional</field>
        </record>
        <record id="blog_tag_2" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">website</field>
        </record>

        <!-- POSTS -->
        <record id="blog_post_1" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">The Future of Emails</field>
            <field name="subtitle">Ideas behind the Odoo communication tools.</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_1"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_1')])]"/>
            <field name="website_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="published_date" eval="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
            <field name="website_meta_keywords">Odoo, email</field>
            <field name="website_meta_description">The Future of Emails</field>
            <field name="cover_properties">{"background-image": "url(/web/image/website_blog.blog_post_cover_01)", "resize_class": "cover container cover_narrow", "background-color": "oe_black", "opacity": "0.0"}</field>
            <field name="content"><![CDATA[
<section class="s_text_block">
    <div class="container">
        <div class="row">
            <div class="col-md-8 col-md-offset-2 mb16 mt16">
                <iframe width="100%" height="250" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/EkbBFmIWoTE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
                <p>
                    Emails are broken.
                </p><p>
                    Emails make me waste my time. But I need them.
                    Given the importance that emails have in our lives,
                    it's incredible it's still one of the only software
                    areas that did not evolve in the past 20 years!
                </p><p>
                    Reading my inbox is the most unproductive task I do
                    on a daily basis. I have to spend one full hour a
                    day to process my emails. All the junk flows in the
                    same inbox; spams, information that doesn't matter,
                    quoted answers of quoted answers, etc. At the end
                    of the hour, only 10 emails actually requested an
                    answer from me. With a good tool, I could have done
                    my job in 10 minutes!
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
</section>
<section class="s_text_block">
    <div class="container">
        <div class="row">
            <div class="col-md-8 col-md-offset-2 mb16 mt16">
                <p>
                    At Odoo, we build tools to bring productivity to
                    enterprises. As emails and information flows are one of
                    the biggest wastes of time in companies, we have to fix
                    this.
                </p><p>
                    To disrupt emails, you need more than just another user
                    interface. We need to rethink the whole communication flow.
                </p>
                <h3>The Communication Mechanism of Odoo</h3>
                <p>
                    Here are the ideas behind the Odoo communication tools:
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        Get Things Done: your inbox is a
                        todo list. You should be able to process (not only
                        read) the inbox and easily mark messages for future
                        actions. Every inbox should be empty after having
                        been processed; no more overload of information.
                        <img class="img-responsive" src="/website_blog/static/src/img/mail-sc-00.png"/>
                    </li><li>
                        Keep control of what you want to receive or don't want
                        to receive. People should never receive spam. You
                        should follow/unfollow any kind of information in one
                        click.
                    </li><li>
                        Productivity is key: our smart user
                        interface does not require you to click on every mail
                        to read a thread. Reading a full thread, replying,
                        attaching documents is super fast.
                        <img class="img-responsive" src="/website_blog/static/src/img/mail-sc-03.png"/>
                    </li><li>
                        A mix of push & pull: Today, people
                        are victims of what others decide to push to them.
                        Odoo differentiates:
                        <ul>
                            <li>
                                Messages "for information":
                                you can pull them when you need some specific
                                information; they are not required to be read
                                every day.You receive only what you decided
                                to follow.This accounts for 90% of your daily
                                emails.Use the "Inbox" menu for these.
                            </li><li>
                                Messages "for action": they
                                require your immediate attention and you need
                                to process them all. This accounts for 10%
                                of your daily emails. Use the "To: me" menu
                                for these.
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                    </li><li>
                        Focus on the Content: Everything is
                        stripped to emphasize on the real message. No more
                        welcome introductions, greetings, signatures and legal
                        notes.We standardize the layout of each message.
                        (signatures are on the profile of a contact, not in
                        every message)
                    </li><li>
                        Folders and mailing lists are great tools but too
                        complex in traditional email clients. In Odoo, a
                        group of contacts that share a discussion can be
                        created with one click. Every group should have it's
                        own email address.
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
</section>
]]>
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="blog_post_2" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">Integrating your CMS and E-Commerce</field>
            <field name="subtitle">Building your company's website and selling your products online easy.</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_1"/>
            <field name="website_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="published_date" eval="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_1'), ref('blog_tag_2')])]"/>
            <field name="cover_properties">{"background-image": "url(/web/image/website_blog.blog_post_cover_02)", "resize_class": "cover container-fluid cover_full", "background-color": "oe_black", "opacity": "0.0"}</field>
            <field name="content"><![CDATA[
<section class="s_image_text">
    <div class="container">
        <div class="row">
            <div class="col-md-6 mt16">
                <img class="img img-responsive mb16" src="/website_blog/static/src/img/CMS_WMS_screens.jpg"/>
            </div>
            <div class="col-md-6 mt16">
                <h3>New Features Launched</h3>

                <p data-chatter-id="counter_0/section/div/div/div">To add to an already comprehensive set of Odoo
                features, a website content management system (CMS or WMS) has been developed and a beta release is
                available from today, 31st January 2014.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
</section>
<section class="s_text_block">
    <div class="container">
        <div class="row">
            <div class="col-md-8 col-md-offset-2 mb16 mt16">
                <p>
                    Odoo claims to be 'the Open Source software that makes
                    building your company's website and selling your products
                    online easy'. So how true is this statement?
                </p><p>
                    "Odoo's latest launch will allow a business to go from
                    zero to trading online quicker than ever before,” Stuart
                    Mackintosh, MD of Open Source specialist and Odoo
                    integration partner, OpusVL, explains. “The investment
                    required to have a fully automated business system is
                    dramatically reduced, enabling the small and medium
                    enterprise to compete at a level of functionality and
                    performance previously reserved for the big IT investors."
                </p>
                <blockquote>
                    <p>
                        "Finally, the leading edge is being brought to the masses.
                        It will now be the turn of the big players to catch up to
                        the superior technologies of the SME."
                    </p>
                </blockquote>
                <p>
                    "This is another clever and highly disruptive move by
                    Odoo,which will force other technology providers to
                    take another look at the value they are providing to ensure
                    that their 'solutions' can still compete."
                </p><p>
                    "Odoo now competes on many fronts, with no real
                    competition out there to knock them off the top spot.
                    With the launch of their integrated CMS and Ecommerce
                    systems,it only elevates their position as one of the leading
                    lights in the open source revolution. It will be at least 5
                    years before another ERP or CMS provider will be able to
                    compete at this level due to the technology currently
                    employed by most industry providers."
                </p>
                <h4>Adding to industry leading technology</h4>
                <p>
                    Like many modern website editors, with Odoo you can edit
                    content in-line, enabling you to see exactly what you are
                    changing and ensure your changes suit the context.
                </p><p>
                    However, unlike other web content management systems, it
                    fully integrates into the back-end database. This means
                    that when you edit a product description, image or price,
                    it updates the product database in real time, providing a
                    true self-service window into the business.
                </p><p>
                    This provides a single source of data for your company and
                    removes the need to create offline synchronisation between
                    website and product database.
                </p><p>
                    As it comes, there is a default website based on Bootstrap
                    3, the latest industry standard for rapid development of
                    multi-device websites backed by Twitter, so can be directly
                    integrated with many web tools and works across all devices
                    by default.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
</section>
]]>
            </field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>
