<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<openerp>
    <!-- <data noupdate="1"> -->
    <data>

        <!-- TAGS -->
        <record id="blog_tag_1" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">functional</field>
        </record>
        <record id="blog_tag_2" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">technical</field>
        </record>
        <record id="blog_tag_3" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">website</field>
        </record>
        <record id="blog_tag_4" model="blog.tag">
            <field name="name">pos</field>
        </record>

        <!-- POSTS -->
        <record id="blog_post_1" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">OpenERP v8 New Features</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_1"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_1')])]"/>
            <field name="website_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="website_meta_keywords">OpenERP, Point of Sale, Hardware, Interface, Payment Terminal, Store</field>
            <field name="website_meta_description">Open source Point of Sale with no installation required that runs online and offline.</field>
            <field name="content"><![CDATA[
        <section data-snippet-id='image-text'>
            <div class="container">
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-6 mt16 mb16">
                        <img class="img-responsive shadow" src="/website/static/src/img/image_text.jpg"/>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-md-6 mt16">
                        <p>
                            OpenERP's Point of Sale introduces a super clean
                            interface with no installation required that runs
                            online and offline on modern hardwares.
                        </p><p>
                            It's full integration with the company inventory
                            and accounting, gives you real time statistics
                            without the hassle of integrating several applications.
                        </p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </section>
        <section class="mt16 mb16" data-snippet-id='text-block'>
            <div class="container">
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 text-center mt16 mb32">
                        <h2>
                            Linked with Project Management
                        </h2>
                        <h3 class="text-muted">Infinitely flexible. Incredibly easy to use.</h3>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb16 mt16">
                        <p>
                            OpenERP's <b>collaborative and realtime</b> project
                            management helps your team get work done. Keep
                            track of everything, from the big picture to the
                            minute details, from the customer contract to the
                            billing.
                        </p><p>
                            Organize projects around <b>your own processes</b>. Work
                            on tasks and issues using the kanban view, schedule
                            tasks using the gantt chart and control deadlines
                            in the calendar view. Every project may have it's
                            own stages allowing teams to optimize their job.
                        </p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </section>
        <section class="oe_dark mt16 mb16" data-snippet-id='big-picture'>
            <div class="container">
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 text-center mt32 mb32">
                        <h2>Work with the hardware you already have...</h2>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-md-12">
                        <img class="img-responsive" src="/website/static/src/img/big_picture.png" style="margin: 0 auto;"/>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-md-6 col-md-offset-3 mb16 mt16">
                        <p class="text-center">
                            <b>No installation required</b>
                        </p>
                        <p class="text-center">
                            OpenERP's Point of Sale introduces a super clean
                            interface with no installation required that runs
                            online and offline on modern hardware. Laptops,
                            tablets, industrial POS, it runs on everything.
                        </p>
                        <p class="text-center">
                            <a href="/page/website.contactus">Get more information »</a>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </section>

]]>
</field>
        </record>

        <record id="blog_post_2" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">New Hardware Integration</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_1"/>
            <field name="website_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_1')])]"/>
            <field name="content">
<![CDATA[<section class="mt16 mb16" data-snippet-id='big-picture'>
            <div class="container">
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12">
                        <img class="img-responsive" src="/website/static/src/img/big_picture.png" style="margin: 0 auto;"/>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-md-6 col-md-offset-3 mb16 mt16">
                        <p class="text-center">
                            <b>New Features Launched</b>
                        </p>
                        <p class="text-center">
                            OpenERP's Point of Sale introduces a super clean
                            interface with no installation required that runs
                            online and offline on modern hardware. Laptops,
                            tablets, industrial POS, it runs on everything.
                        </p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </section>
        <section data-snippet-id='pricing'>
            <div class="container">
              <div class="row">
                <div class="col-md-12 text-center mt16 mb32">
                    <h2>Our Offers</h2>
                </div>

                <div class="col-md-4">
                    <div class="panel panel-info">
                      <!-- Default panel contents -->
                      <div class="panel-heading text-center">
                          <h2 style="margin: 0">Beginner</h2>
                          <p style="margin: 0" class="text-muted">
                              Starter package
                          </p>
                      </div>
                      <div class="panel-body text-center text-muted" style="background-color: rgba(0,0,0,0.1)">
                        <h2 style="margin: 0"><span>$</span><b style="font-size: 60px">450</b><small>.00</small></h2>
                        <div>per month</div>
                      </div>

                      <!-- List group -->
                      <ul class="list-group">
                        <li class="list-group-item">Battery: 8 hours</li>
                        <li class="list-group-item">Screen: 2.5 inch</li>
                        <li class="list-group-item">Weight: 1.1 ounces</li>
                        <li class="list-group-item">No support</li>
                      </ul>
                      <div class="panel-footer text-center">
                          <p class="text-muted">
                              <i>Free shipping, satisfied or reimbursed.</i>
                          </p>
                          <a href="/page/website.contactus" class="btn btn-primary btn-lg">Order now</a>
                      </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="col-md-4">
                    <div class="panel panel-primary">
                      <!-- Default panel contents -->
                      <div class="panel-heading text-center">
                          <h2 style="margin: 0">Professional</h2>
                          <p style="margin: 0">
                              Enterprise package
                          </p>
                      </div>
                      <div class="panel-body text-center text-muted" style="background-color: rgba(0,0,0,0.1)">
                        <h2 style="margin: 0"><span>$</span><b style="font-size: 60px">590</b><small>.00</small></h2>
                        <div>per month</div>
                      </div>

                      <!-- List group -->
                      <ul class="list-group">
                        <li class="list-group-item">Battery: 12 hours</li>
                        <li class="list-group-item">Screen: 2.8 inch</li>
                        <li class="list-group-item">Weight: 1.2 ounces</li>
                        <li class="list-group-item">Limited support</li>
                      </ul>
                      <div class="panel-footer text-center">
                          <p class="text-muted">
                              <i>Free shipping, satisfied or reimbursed.</i>
                          </p>
                          <a href="/page/website.contactus" class="btn btn-primary btn-lg">Order now</a>
                      </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="col-md-4">
                    <div class="panel panel-info">
                      <!-- Default panel contents -->
                      <div class="panel-heading text-center">
                          <h2 style="margin: 0">Expert</h2>
                          <p style="margin: 0" class="text-muted">
                              The top of the top
                          </p>
                      </div>
                      <div class="panel-body text-center text-muted" style="background-color: rgba(0,0,0,0.1)">
                        <h2 style="margin: 0"><span>$</span><b style="font-size: 60px">890</b><small>.00</small></h2>
                        <div>per month</div>
                      </div>

                      <!-- List group -->
                      <ul class="list-group">
                        <li class="list-group-item">Battery: 20 hours</li>
                        <li class="list-group-item">Screen: 2.8 inch</li>
                        <li class="list-group-item">Weight: 1.2 ounces</li>
                        <li class="list-group-item">Unlimited support</li>
                      </ul>
                      <div class="panel-footer text-center">
                          <p class="text-muted">
                              <i>Free shipping, satisfied or reimbursed.</i>
                          </p>
                          <a href="/page/website.contactus" class="btn btn-primary btn-lg">Contact us</a>
                      </div>
                    </div>

                </div>
              </div>
            </div>
        </section>


]]>
</field>
        </record>
        <record id="blog_post_3" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">Sorry SAP Campaign - The Making Of</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_1"/>
            <field name="website_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="website_meta_keywords">OpenERP, News, Sorry SAP</field>
            <field name="website_meta_description">Sorry SAP Campaign - The Making Of</field>
            <field name="content"><![CDATA[
        <section data-snippet-id="text" class="readable">
            <div class="container">
                <p>I needed to change the world. I wanted to ... You know how it
                is when you are young; you have big dreams, a lot of energy 
                and naïve stupidity. My dream was to lead the enterprise 
                management market with a fully open source software. (I also 
                wanted to get 100 employees before 30 years old with a 
                self-financed company but I failed this one by a few months).
                </p>
            </div>
        </section>
        <section data-snippet-id="text-image" class="readable">
            <div class="container">
                <p>To fuel my motivation, I had to pick someone to fight 
                against. In business, it's like a playground. When you arrive in
                a new school, if you want to quickly become the leader, you must
                choose the class bully, the older guy who terrorises small boys,
                and kick his butt in front of everyone. That was my strategy 
                with SAP, the enterprise software giant.</p>
                <p>So, in 2005, I started to develop the TinyERP product, the 
                software that (at least in my mind) would change the enterprise 
                world. While preparing for the "day of the fight" in 2006, I 
                bought the SorrySAP.com domain name. I put it on hold for 6 
                years, waiting for the right moment to use it. I thought it 
                would take 3 years to deprecate a 77 billion dollars company 
                just because open source is so cool. Sometimes it's better for 
                your self-motivation not to face reality...</p>
                <p>To make things happen, I worked hard, very hard. I worked 13 
                hours a day, 7 days a week, with no vacations for 7 years.I 
                lost friendships and broke up with my girlfriend in the process 
                (fortunately, I found a more valuable wife now. I will explain 
                later why she is worth 1 million EUR :).</p>
                <p>Three years later, I discovered you can't change the world 
                if you are "tiny". Especially if the United States is part of 
                this world, where it's better to be a BigERP, rather than a 
                TinyERP. Can you imagine how small you feel in front of Danone's
                directors asking; "but why should we pay millions of dollars 
                for a tiny software?" So, we renamed TinyERP to OpenERP.</p>
                <p>As we worked hard, things started to evolve. We were 
                developing dozens of modules for OpenERP, the open source 
                community was growing and I was even able to pay all employees' 
                salaries at the end of the month without fear (which was a 
                situation I struggled with for 4 years).</p>
                <p>In 2010, we had a 100+ employees company selling services on 
                OpenERP and a powerful but ugly product. This is what happens 
                when delivering services to customers distracts you from 
                building an exceptional product.</p>
                <p>It was time to do a pivot in the business model.</p>
                <h3>The Pivot</h3>
                <p>We wanted to switch from a service company to a software 
                publisher company. This would allow to increase our efforts in 
                our research and development activities. As a result, we 
                changed our business model and decided to stop our services to 
                customers and focus on building a strong partner network and 
                maintenance offer. This would cost money, so I had to raise a 
                few million euros.</p>
                <p>After a few months of pitching investors, I got roughly 10 
                LOI from different VCs. We chosed Sofinnova Partners, the 
                biggest European VC, and Xavier Niel the founder of Iliad, the 
                only company in France funded in the past 10 years to have 
                reached the 1 billion euro valuation.</p>
                <p>I signed the LOI. I didn't realize that this contract could 
                have turned me into a homeless person. (I already had a dog, 
                all I needed was to lose a lot of money to become homeless). 
                The fund raising was based on a company valuation but there 
                was a financial mechanism to re-evaluate the company up by 
                9.8 m€ depending on the turnover of the next 4 years. I should 
                have received warrants convertible into shares if we achieved 
                the turnover targeted in the business plan.</p>
                <p>The night before receiving the warrants in front of the 
                notary, my wife checked the contracts. She asked me what would 
                be the taxation on these warrants. I rang the lawyer and guess 
                what? Belgium is probably the only country in the world where 
                you have to pay taxes on warrants when you receive them, even 
                if you never reach the conditions to convert them into shares. 
                If I had accepted these warrants, I would have had to pay a 
                12.5% tax on 9.8 m€; resulting in a tax of 1.2m€ to pay in 18 
                months! So, my wife is worth 1.2 million EUR. I would have 
                ended up a homeless person without her, as I still did not 
                have a salary at that time.</p> 
                <p>We changed the deal and I got the 3 million EUR. It allowed 
                me to recruit a rocking management team.</p>
                <img class="img-responsive shadow" src="/website/static/src/img/OpemERP_board.jpg"/>
                <h3 class="mt16">Being a mature company<h3>
                <p>With this money in our bank account, we boosted two 
                departments: R&D and Sales. We burned two million EUR in 18 months, 
                mostly in salaries. The company started to grow even faster. 
                We developed a partner network of 500 partners in 100 countries 
                and we started to sign contracts with 6 zeros.</p>
                <p>Then, things became different. You know, tedious things like 
                handling human resources, board meetings, dealing with big 
                customer contracts, traveling to launch international 
                subsidiaries. We did boring stuff like budgets, career paths, 
                management meetings, etc.</p>
                <p>2011 was a complex year. We did not meet our expectations: 
                we only achieved 70% of the forecasted sales budget. Our 
                management meetings were tense. We under performed. We were not 
                satisfied with ourselves. We had a constant feeling that we 
                missed something. It's a strange feeling to build extraordinary 
                things but to not be proud of ourselves.</p>
                <p>But one day, someone (I don't remember who, I have a 
                goldfish memory) made a graph of the monthly turnover of the 
                past 2 years. It was like waking up from a nighmare. In fact, 
                it was not that bad, we had multiplied by 10 the monthly turnover 
                over the span of roughly two years! This is when we understood 
                that OpenERP is a marathon, not a sprint. Only 100% growth a 
                year is ok... if you can keep the rhythm for several years.</p> 
                <img class="img-responsive shadow" src="/website/static/src/img/turnover_updated.png"/>
                <p class="text-center" section_inner="1">
                <strong>OpenERP Monthly Turnover</strong></p>
                <p>As usual, I should have listened to my wife. She is way more 
                lucid than I am. Every week I complained to her "it's not good 
                enough, we should grow faster, what am I missing?" and she used 
                to reply; "But you already are the fastest growing company in 
                Belgium!". (Deloitte awarded us as the fastest growing company 
                of Belgium with 1549% growth of the turnover between 2007 and 
                2011)</p> 
                <h3 class="mt16">Changing the world</h3>
                <p>Then, the dream started to become reality. We started to get 
                clues that what we did would change the world:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>With 1.000 installations per day, we became the most 
                    installed management software in the world,</li>
                    <li>Analysts from Big 4 started to prefer OpenERP over SAP,</li>
                    <li>OpenERP is now a compulsory subject for the 
                    baccalaureate in France like Word, Excel and Powerpoint</li>
                    <li>60 new modules are released every month (we became the 
                    wikipedia of the management software thanks to our strong 
                    community)</li>
                </ul>
                <p>Something is happening... And it's big!</p>
                <p>OpenERP 7.0 is about to be released and I know you will be 
                astonished by it.</p>
                <p>The official release is planned for the 21th of December. 
                As the Mayas predicted it, this is the end of an age, the old 
                ERP dinosaurs.</p>
                <p>It's time to pull out the Ace: the SorrySAP.com domain name 
                that I bought 6 years ago.</p>
                <p>If you want to test the v7 version online, just go the homepage.</p>
            </div>
        </section>
 ]]>
</field>
        </record>
        
        <record id="blog_post_4" model="blog.post">
            <field name="name">Announcing a New Partnership</field>
            <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_1"/>
            <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_1')])]"/>
            <field name="website_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="website_meta_keywords">OpenERP, Partnership, News, Accounting</field>
            <field name="website_meta_description">Our company partners with OpenERP to develop accounting best practices.</field>
            <field name="content"><![CDATA[
        <section data-snippet-id='image-text'>
            <div class="container">
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-6 mt16 mb16">
                        <img class="img-responsive shadow" src="/website/static/src/img/text_image.png"/>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-md-6 mt16">
                        <p>
                            We are proud to announce a new partnership with
                            the company OpenERP. Their open source application suite
                            will allow us to reach new markets, specifically in
                            the accounting area.
                        </p><p>
                            The full integration with the company inventory
                            and accounting, will give our customers real time statistics
                            without the hassle of integrating several applications.
                        </p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </section>
        <section class="mt16 mb16" data-snippet-id='text-block'>
            <div class="container">
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 text-center mt16 mb32">
                        <h2>
                            OpenERP Project Management
                        </h2>
                        <h3 class="text-muted">Infinitely flexible. Incredibly easy to use.</h3>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb16 mt16">
                        <p>
                            OpenERP's <b>collaborative and realtime</b> project
                            management helps your team get work done. Keep
                            track of everything, from the big picture to the
                            minute details, from the customer contract to the
                            billing.
                        </p><p>
                            Organize projects around <b>your own processes</b>. Work
                            on tasks and issues using the kanban view, schedule
                            tasks using the gantt chart and control deadlines
                            in the calendar view. Every project may have it's
                            own stages allowing teams to optimize their job.
                        </p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </section>
]]>
</field>
        </record>


    </data>
</openerp>
