<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- vim:fdn=3:
-->
<openerp>
    <data>
        <template id="assets_backend" name="account assets" inherit_id="web.assets_backend">
            <xpath expr="." position="inside">
                <link rel="stylesheet" href="/account/static/src/css/account_move_reconciliation.css"/>
                <link rel="stylesheet" href="/account/static/src/css/account_move_line_quickadd.css"/>
                <link rel="stylesheet" href="/account/static/src/css/account_bank_and_cash.css"/>
                <script type="text/javascript" src="/account/static/src/js/account_move_reconciliation.js"></script>
                <script type="text/javascript" src="/account/static/src/js/account_move_line_quickadd.js"></script>
            </xpath>
        </template>
        
        <template id="help_action_account_fiscalyear">
		      <p class="oe_view_nocontent_create">
		         Click to start a new fiscal year.
		      </p><p>
		        Define your company's financial year according to your needs. A
		        financial year is a period at the end of which a company's
		        accounts are made up (usually 12 months). The financial year is
		        usually referred to by the date in which it ends. For example,
		        if a company's financial year ends November 30, 2011, then
		        everything between December 1, 2010 and November 30, 2011
		        would be referred to as FY 2011.
		      </p>
        </template>
        <template id="help_action_account_period">
        	  <p class="oe_view_nocontent_create">
                Click to add a fiscal period.
              </p><p>
                An accounting period typically is a month or a quarter. It
                usually corresponds to the periods of the tax declaration.
              </p>
        </template>
        <template id="help_action_account_form">
              <p class="oe_view_nocontent_create">
                Click to add an account.
              </p><p>
                An account is part of a ledger allowing your company
                to register all kinds of debit and credit transactions.
                Companies present their annual accounts in two main parts: the
                balance sheet and the income statement (profit and loss
                account). The annual accounts of a company are required by law
                to disclose a certain amount of information.
              </p>
        </template>
        <template id="help_action_account_gain_loss">
              <p class="oe_view_nocontent_create">
                Click to add an account.
              </p><p>
                When doing multi-currency transactions, you may loose or gain
                some amount due to changes of exchange rate. This menu gives
                you a forecast of the Gain or Loss you'd realized if those
                transactions were ended today. Only for accounts having a
                secondary currency set.
              </p>
        </template>
        <template id="help_action_account_journal_form">
             <p class="oe_view_nocontent_create">
                Click to add a journal.
              </p><p>
                A journal is used to record transactions of all accounting data
                related to the day-to-day business.
              </p><p>
                A typical company may use one journal per payment method (cash,
                bank accounts, checks), one purchase journal, one sale journal
                and one for miscellaneous information.
              </p>
        </template>
        <template id="help_action_bank_statement_tree">
              <p class="oe_view_nocontent_create">
                Click to register a bank statement.
              </p><p>
                A bank statement is a summary of all financial transactions
                occurring over a given period of time on a bank account. You
                should receive this periodicaly from your bank.
              </p><p>
                OpenERP allows you to reconcile a statement line directly with
                the related sale or puchase invoices.
              </p>
        </template>
        <template id="help_action_account_type_form"> 
              <p class="oe_view_nocontent_create">
                Click to define a new account type.
              </p><p>
                An account type is used to determine how an account is used in
                each journal. The deferral method of an account type determines
                the process for the annual closing. Reports such as the Balance
                Sheet and the Profit and Loss report use the category
                (profit/loss or balance sheet).
              </p>
        </template>
        <template id="help_action_tax_code_list"> 
              <p class="oe_view_nocontent_create">
                Click to define a new tax code.
              </p><p>
                Depending on the country, a tax code is usually a cell to fill
                in your legal tax statement. OpenERP allows you to define the
                tax structure and each tax computation will be registered in
                one or several tax code.
              </p>
        </template>
        <template id="help_action_account_moves_all_a"> 
              <p class="oe_view_nocontent_create">
                Select the period and the journal you want to fill.
              </p><p>
                This view can be used by accountants in order to quickly record
                entries in OpenERP. If you want to record a supplier invoice,
                start by recording the line of the expense account. OpenERP
                will propose to you automatically the Tax related to this
                account and the counterpart "Account Payable".
              </p>
        </template>
        <template id="help_action_account_manual_reconcile"> 
              <p>
                 No journal items found.
              </p>
        </template>
        <template id="help_action_move_journal_line"> 
              <p class="oe_view_nocontent_create">
                Click to create a journal entry.
              </p><p>
                A journal entry consists of several journal items, each of
                which is either a debit or a credit transaction.
              </p><p>
                OpenERP automatically creates one journal entry per accounting
                document: invoice, refund, supplier payment, bank statements,
                etc. So, you should record journal entries manually only/mainly
                for miscellaneous operations.
              </p>
        </template>
        <template id="help_action_subscription_form"> 
              <p class="oe_view_nocontent_create">
                Click to define a new recurring entry.
              </p><p>
                A recurring entry occurs on a recurrent basis from a specific
                date, i.e. corresponding to the signature of a contract or an
                agreement with a customer or a supplier. You can create such
                entries to automate the postings in the system.
              </p>
        </template>
        <template id="help_action_view_bank_statement_tree"> 
              <p class="oe_view_nocontent_create">
                Click to create a new cash log.
              </p><p>
                A Cash Register allows you to manage cash entries in your cash
                journals. This feature provides an easy way to follow up cash
                payments on a daily basis. You can enter the coins that are in
                your cash box, and then post entries when money comes in or
                goes out of the cash box.
              </p>
        </template>
    </data>
</openerp>