<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<openerp>
    <data noupdate="1">
        <record id="base.user_demo" model="res.users">
            <field eval="[(4, ref('base.group_sale_salesman')),(4, ref('base.group_document_user'))]" name="groups_id"/>
        </record>
        
        <record id="document_google_docs" model="document.page">
            <field name="name">OpenERP 6.1. Functional Demo</field>
            <field name="minor_edit">0</field>
            <field name="index">6</field>
            <field name="summary">Initial Page</field>
            <field  name="content">==OpenERP 6.1. Functional Demo==
            	
The news is out, OpenERP's latest version 6.1. is here.
It's more user-friendly, even more business oriented and efficient to manage your company

How to discover the latest version 6.1.?

Demo : [http://demo.openerp.com]
Online: [http://openerp.com/online]
Download: [http://openerp.com/downloads]

We have also put together a functional demo that presents 6.1. Watch this video to learn directly from us what OpenERP 6.1. can do for you. Share it in your company, with your clients and implement it now for your business.

==Watch on Youtube!==

[[Video:http://www.youtube.com/embed/7jES2jxKMso ]]

</field>
</record>

<record id="document_dashboards" model="document.page">
            <field name="name">Personalise Dashboards</field>
            <field name="minor_edit">0</field>
            <field name="index">7</field>
            <field name="summary">Initial Page</field>
            <field  name="content">==Personalise your OpenERP dashboards==
You like OpenERP, but feel like you want to personalise it more? Now, OpenERP goes a step further and lets you customize your dashboard.
How? you will ask. Thanks to a new feature that allows you to customize your dashboard by adding new boards of any search view.

Let's say you are not a big fan of the default dashboard and you feel like the view provided are not the most relevant to you. So, now you can remove the board you find useless and customize your own one. 

==How is it done?==

Step 1: access one search view 

Step 2: apply the filter you want to see at each connection to the application (eg. on sales, manufacturing, etc)

Step 3: add it into the dashboard in the same space where you can save the filter

Step 4: choose the application you want it visible on and the name of the array

Look at this simple example below from Purchase, where I want to put on the application's dashboard "Purchases to Approve". After I access the search view and apply the filter for "Purchases to Approve", I can add it immediately to my Purchase dashboard.


[[File:http://www.openerp.com/sites/default/files/fileattach/dashboard2_1(1).png ]]

In less than a minute, the search view is visible on the dashboard

[[File:http://www.openerp.com/sites/default/files/fileattach/dashboard2_2.png ]]

Of course, you are free to delete what you don't need or like, but just in case you change your mind there is a reset button to return to the default view.
</field>
</record>

<record id="document_pos" model="document.page">
            <field name="name">Touchscreen Point of Sale</field>
            <field name="minor_edit">0</field>
            <field name="index">8</field>
            <field name="summary">Initial Page</field>
            <field  name="content">==The new OpenERP touchscreen Point of Sale==
            	
The brand new OpenERP touchscreen point of sale available with 6.1 allows you to manage your shop sales very easily.
It's fully web based so that you don't have to install or deploy any software and all the sales shops can be easily consolidated.
It works in connected and disconnected modes so that you can continue to sell if you lose your internet connection.

[[File:http://www.openerp.com/sites/default/files/fileattach/POS(2).png ]]

==Here's a summary of its main features and benefits:==

100% WEB based

available for any touchscreen device (ipod, ipad, any tablet)mobile (with portable devices)

no installation required
Packed as a standard OpenERP module

no synchronization needed, completely integrated
all OpenERP available, use OpenERP for backend consolidate shops almost in real time
Work offline, with no server connection

continue working even when your connection is down
if you close your browser, data won't be lost

fully web based with a clean interface smart interface
You have different options to select your products. You can do it through the barcode reader, just browse through the categories you have put in place (ie. drinks, snacks, meals, etc.), or text search in case neither of the other options work for you.
If you need to use the POS for your restaurant, for example, your employees can record at the same time multiple tickets without having to wait to do one transaction at a time. Along, to facilitate payment, the application allows multiple payment methods.

The POS application is so simple and accessible to use that your shop or restaurant will never need any other tool to manage orders. Due to its smart and user-friendly interface you don't need any training to learn how to use it. Think of it as an out-of-the-box solution to boost your business' productivity.
	</field>
</record>
        
    </data>
</openerp>