<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>

    <record id="base.partner_admin" model="res.partner">
        <field name="is_published">True</field>
    </record>
    <record id="base.partner_demo" model="res.partner">
        <field name="is_published">True</field>
    </record>
    <record id="base.partner_demo_portal" model="res.partner">
        <field name="is_published">True</field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_2" model="res.partner">
        <field name="is_published">True</field>
        <field name="website_short_description">Axelor is a service company specializing in the integration of Open Source ERP. She is co-editor including the web version of Odoo and concentrates all its activities to Odoo integration and implementation of supply...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[Axelor is a service company specializing in the integration of Open Source ERP. She is co-editor including the web version of Odoo and concentrates all its activities to Odoo integration and implementation of supply Saas (ASP) based on Odoo. Axelor can now claim many references to Odoo implementations in various industries.<br/> <br/>
The company has its own R&D performing many innovations to the continuous improvement of Odoo, such as the new web version, the plug-in MS Office and connectors to other applications. Its main advantages are its integration methodology and rigor to the management of major projects for the audit and design phase up to production and customer support.]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_1" model="res.partner">
        <field name="is_published">True</field>
        <field name="website_short_description">3 good reasons to choose today for Federal as partners for the implementation of your ERP project: Firstly, you have a software specialist, secondly, a hardware and performance specialist AND thirdly a business economist with expertise in project management. And...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[3 good reasons to choose today for Federal as partners for the implementation of your ERP project:
Firstly, you have a software specialist, secondly, a hardware and performance specialist AND thirdly a business economist with expertise in project management. And what does this mean for you? It's simple ...<br/>
… Your individual requirements are mapped into the standard software<br/>
… professional design of the optimal sizing for your system landscape<br/>
… Understanding of commercial and logistical processes in your business and engaging your staff and efficient use of resources.<br/><br/>
Above all, you need reliable and professional advisors who will listen to your challenges seriously and implement adapted solutions. Welcome to Federal!]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_4" model="res.partner">
        <field name="is_published">True</field>
        <field name="website_short_description">Global Solutions helps organisations of all shapes and sizes gain a competitive advantage through Free and Open Source software. Our experienced team can provide strategic advice, implementation, integration with exis...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[Global Solutions helps organisations of all shapes and sizes gain a competitive advantage through Free and Open Source software. Our experienced team can provide strategic advice, implementation, integration with existing systems, hosting and support services for a wide range of open source applications. Working with our customers Global Solutions helps to select and deliver best-of-breed solutions using Open Source products. Key skills and partnerships include Ubuntu, vtiger CRM, OpenEMM, Alfresco and of course Odoo.
 <br/> <br/>
Founded in 2006, our clients range from SMEs to globally recognised brands and public sector organisations.]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_3" model="res.partner">
        <field name="is_published">True</field>
        <field name="website_short_description">Millennium Industries is a London based Odoo partner.  Their specialist areas include accounting, CRM, manufacturing, stock, logistics, and supply chain management.  The company has completed over 15 projects with intric...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[Millennium Industries is a London based Odoo partner.  Their specialist areas include accounting, CRM, manufacturing, stock, logistics, and supply chain management.  The company has completed over 15 projects with intricate consolidation and stock-accounting requirements for which they can provide references. <br/> <br/>
 
Millennium Industries have developed several accounting modules for Odoo and are the leading experts in the UK for this area.  Additionally, a forefront success story of theirs is the nominal level data migrations from Sage Line 50 to Odoo that allows unprecedented efficiency in system switchover. <br/> <br/>
 
Last but not least, Millennium Industries is the only UK partner with their own Europe-based fully staffed development centre, aimed to deliver to the exact client specification projects of any complexity. <br/> <br/>
Please contact Millennium Industries direct to discuss your business requirement and the company would be delighted to help.]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_10" model="res.partner">
        <field name="is_published">True</field>
        <field name="website_short_description">The Jackson Group is an active and leading partner of Odoo in the US. As Odoo's longest active US partner, we help our clients leverage new methods, cost-effective tools and fresh technologies to simplify infrastructure, lower cost, and improve operations. Our goal is to help our clients become...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[The Jackson Group is an active and leading partner of Odoo in the US.
As Odoo's longest active US partner, we help our clients leverage new methods, cost-effective tools and fresh technologies to simplify infrastructure, lower cost, and improve operations.<br/> <br/>
Our goal is to help our clients become high-performing, competitive and profitable businesses.
We leverage robust model that combines:<br/>
<ul><li>
Implementations of feature rich, extensible, and cost-effective Open Source software (Odoo) </li>
<li>Experienced consulting services </li>
<li>Domestic US, near-shore and offshore based resources </li>
<li>A highly-responsive support model </li>
<li>A strategy that drives US Localization and adds new capabilities to Odoo </li>
</ul><br/><br/>
 
The Jackson Group’s Odoo consulting services include: <br/>
<ul> <li>
Roadmap Development </li>
<li>Program/Project Management </li>
<li>Process Analysis </li>
<li>Implementation and Configuration (on-premise or on-demand environments) </li>
<li>Data Migration </li>
<li>Programming and Custom Module Development </li>
<li>Training</li>
<li>Support </li>
<li>Managed Services</li>]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_18" model="res.partner">
        <field name="is_published">True</field>
        <field name="website_short_description">We are a technology consulting &amp; strategic advisory firm that creates value enhancing solutions through the use of advanced software for our clients worldwide. At Lumber Inc we bring operational experience combined...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[We are a technology consulting & strategic advisory firm that creates value enhancing solutions through the use of advanced software for our clients worldwide.
 <br/> <br/>
At Lumber Inc we bring operational experience combined with technological acumen. We understand that any software that supports business operations needs to be designed in such a way that facilitates the execution of critical operational processes, and serves as a tool to the users rather than a barrier. Our approach is focused on the process first, ensuring that it contributes to the goals of the company, we then optimize it, and design the software solutions to best support it.]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="base.res_partner_12" model="res.partner">
        <field name="is_published">True</field>
        <field name="website_short_description">Best Designers is an IT services organization, established by 3 industry experts headquartered at Mumbai, India. The organization serve customers with Open Source Enterprise Software applications. We are specialized in...</field>
        <field name="website_description"><![CDATA[Best Designers is an IT services organization, established by 3 industry experts headquartered at Mumbai, India. The organization serve customers with Open Source Enterprise Software applications. We are specialized in <b>ERP Implementation, CRM Implementation, E-Commerce to ERP Integrations, Document Management Systems and Open Source Training.</b> Our key products include <b>Odoo, Alfresco and Magento.</b> Our core objective is to deliver quality in <b>Odoo Implementation Services</b> incorporating supreme value to enterprises globally, at an affordable price. Our experience in managing projects right from selecting tools and platforms to implement solutions has shown results in <b>Reducing IT Budgets for SME making Technology Affordable. </b>
 <br/> <br/>
Our ERP expertise is since 2005 and we mainly focus on Odoo Implementation across the globe, being an <b>Off-shore Development Partner from India</b>, we are also associated with other Odoo Partners across the globe to implement Odoo Business Applications. In order to provide world class ERP, E–Commerce and Enterprise Solutions, we have designed innovative Implementation Methodologies and concepts, which help us provide reliable business solutions that meet present as well as future demands.
<br/><br/>
Best Designers has now emerged serving the Small and Medium Business – SMB’s with lots of Free and Open Source Software's, Our team is proficient to deliver quick and quality solutions. With a blend of experts with proven track record, our enterprise solution Business Consultants, ERP Consultants, Network Engineers, Software Developers, Web Architects, Software Testers and Search Engine Optimizers makes it possible to offer our clients affordable solutions that are both innovative and highly influential.
]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
