<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<openerp>
    <data>

    <record id="event_sale.event_technical_training" model="event.event">
        <field name="website_published">True</field>
        <field name="description_website"><![CDATA[
<center><strong>OpenERP v.7 Technical Training in English (5 days)</strong></center>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Course summary:</strong></p>
<p>This course is dedicated to partners, integrators and developers who need to grasp knowledge of the OpenERP development process. This course is for new developers or for IT professionals eager to learn more about the OpenERP technical aspects.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Objectives:</strong></p>
<p>Having attended this course, participants should be able to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Understand the development concepts and architecture;</li>
<li>Install and administer OpenERP;</li>
<li>Develop a new OpenERP module.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Our prices include:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>drinks and lunch;</li>
<li>training material.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Requirements:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Bring your own laptop.</li>
<li>Participants are expected to have some knowledge in programming.&nbsp;A basic knowledge of the Python programming is recommended.</li>
<li>Participants preferably have a functional knowledge of the OpenERP software (see Functional Training).</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>For more information on the program, please explore <a href="http://www.openerp.com/services/technical-training">http://www.openerp.com/services/technical-training</a>.</p>
<p>If you have a question<strong>&nbsp;concerning the content of the training</strong>, please contact <a href="mailto:training@openerp.com">training@openerp.com</a>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Where to find us:</strong></p>
<p>Chaussée de Namur 40, 1367 Ramillies (Belgium)</p>
<p>More information about our Headquarter office (directions, transports, parking, hotels, ...), please have a look at&nbsp;<a href="http://bit.ly/VD8J67">http://bit.ly/VD8J67.</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Cancellation Policy:&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>The organization of the training session has related costs. Due to these costs, cancellations made less than 2 weeks (14 calendar days) prior to the start of the training session is a subject to a fee. This fee can be up to a maximum of 1000€ per cancellation request.</p>
<p>We strongly recommend to book your flight tickets and/or hotel reservations 2 weeks prior to the training. If the training is cancelled 2 weeks in advance, you'll be notified by email.</p>
<div>&nbsp;</div>
<p>For any additional information, please contact us at <a href="mailto:events@openerp.com">events@openerp.com</a>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Best regards,</p>
<p>Miss Charline Louis, OpenERP Junior Event Manager</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p align="RIGHT"><em>(OpenERP reserves the right to cancel, re-name or re-locate<br/>the event or change the dates on which it is held.)</em></p>
]]></field>
    </record>

    </data>
</openerp>
