<templates>
    <t t-name="ImportView">
        <t t-set="_id" t-value="_.uniqueId('export')"/>
        <form action="" method="post" enctype="multipart/form-data" class="oe_import">
            <div class="oe_view_manager oe_view_manager_current">
                <div class="oe_view_manager_header oe_padding">
                    <h2>
                        Import a CSV File
                    </h2>
                    <input type="hidden" name="session_id"
                       t-att-value="widget.session.session_id"/>
                    <input type="hidden" name="import_id"/>
                    <button type="button" disabled="disabled"
                            class="oe_button oe_import_button oe_import_validate oe_highlight"
                        >Validate</button>
                    <button type="button" disabled="disabled"
                            class="oe_button oe_import_button oe_import_import"
                        >Import</button>
                    <span class="oe_fade">or</span>
                    <a class="oe_import_cancel" href="#">Cancel</a>
                </div>
            </div>

            <p>Select the <a
                    href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Comma-separated_values"
                    class="oe_import_csv" target="_blank">.CSV</a>
            file to import. If you need a sample importable file, you
            can use the export tool to generate one.</p>
            <div class="oe_import_box">
                <label t-attf-for="file_#{_id}" autofocus="autofocus">CSV File:</label>
                <input type="file" id-attf-id="file_#{_id}"
                       name="file" class="oe_import_file"/>
                <button type="button" class="oe_import_file_reload"
                        disabled="disabled"
                        title="Reload data to check changes.">
                    <img src="/web/static/src/img/icons/gtk-refresh.png"/>
                </button>
                <div class="oe_import_with_file">
                    <a href="#" class="oe_import_toggle">
                        File Format Options…</a>
                    <div class="oe_import_toggled oe_import_options">
                        <p t-foreach="widget.opts" t-as="option">
                            <!-- no @name, avoid submission when file_update called -->
                            <label t-attf-for="#{option.name}_#{_id}">
                                <t t-esc="option.label"/></label>
                            <input t-attf-id="#{option.name}_#{_id}"
                                   t-attf-class="oe_import_#{option.name}"
                                   t-att-value="option.value"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>

            <div class="oe_import_with_file oe_padding">
                <h2>Map your data to Odoo</h2>
                <div title="If the model uses openchatter, history tracking
                            will set up subscriptions and send notifications
                            during the import, but lead to a slower import.">
                    <input type="checkbox" id="oe_import_tracking"
                           checked="checked"/>
                    <label for="oe_import_tracking">
                        Track history during import
                    </label>
                </div>
                <input type="checkbox" class="oe_import_has_header"
                       id="oe_import_has_header" checked="checked"/>
                <label for="oe_import_has_header">The first row of the
                file contains the label of the column</label>
                <p class="oe_import_noheaders">If the file contains
                the column names, Odoo can try auto-detecting the
                field corresponding to the column. This makes imports
                simpler especially when the file has many columns.</p>

                <div class="oe_import_error_report"></div>
                <table class="oe_import_grid" />
            </div>
            <div class="oe_padding">
                <h2>Frequently Asked Questions</h2>

                <dl>
                    <dt><a href="#" class="oe_import_toggle">
                        Need to import data from an other application?</a></dt>
                    <dd>
                        <p>In order to re-create relationships between
                        different records, you should use the unique
                        identifier from the original application and
                        map it to the <abbr title="External ID">ID</abbr>
                        column in Odoo. When you
                        import an other record that links to the first
                        one, use <abbr title="XXX/External ID">XXX/ID</abbr>
                        to the original unique identifier.</p>
                        <p>The <abbr title="External ID">ID</abbr>
                        will also be used to update the original
                        import if you need to re-import modified data
                        later, it's thus good practice to specify it
                        whenever possible</p>
                    </dd>
                </dl>

                <dl>
                    <dt><a href="#" class="oe_import_toggle">
                        What can I do when the Import preview table isn't 
                        displayed correctly?</a></dt>
                    <dd>
                        <p>By default the Import preview is set on commas as 
                        field separators and quotation marks as text 
                        delimiters. If your csv file does not have these 
                        settings, you can modify the File Format Options 
                        (displayed under the Browse CSV file bar after you 
                        select your file).</p> <p>Note that if your CSV file 
                        has a tabulation as separator, Odoo will not 
                        detect the separations. You will need to change the 
                        file format options in your spreadsheet application. 
                        See the following question.</p>
                    </dd>
                </dl>

                <dl>
                    <dt><a href="#" class="oe_import_toggle">
                        How can I change the CSV file format options when 
                        saving in my spreadsheet application?</a></dt>
                    <dd>
                        <p>If you edit and save CSV files in speadsheet 
                        applications, your computer's regional settings will 
                        be applied for the separator and delimiter. 
                        We suggest you use OpenOffice or LibreOffice Calc 
                        as they will allow you to modify all three options 
                        (in 'Save As' dialog box > Check the box 'Edit filter 
                        settings' > Save).</p> <p>Microsoft Excel will allow 
                        you to modify only the encoding when saving 
                        (in 'Save As' dialog box > click 'Tools' dropdown 
                        list > Encoding tab).</p>
                    </dd>
                </dl>

                <dl>
                    <dt><a href="#" class="oe_import_toggle">
                        What's the difference between Database ID and 
                        External ID?</a></dt>
                    <dd>
                        <p>Some fields define a relationship with another 
                        object. For example, the country of a contact is a 
                        link to a record of the 'Country' object. When you 
                        want to import such fields, Odoo will have to 
                        recreate links between the different records. 
                        To help you import such fields, Odoo provides 3 
                        mechanisms. You must use one and only one mechanism 
                        per field you want to import.</p> <p>For example, to 
                        reference the country of a contact, Odoo proposes 
                        you 3 different fields to import: <ul>
                        <li>Country: the name or code of the country</li>
                        <li>Country/Database ID: the unique Odoo ID for a 
                        record, defined by the ID postgresql column</li>
                        <li>Country/External ID: the ID of this record 
                        referenced in another application (or the .XML file 
                        that imported it)</li> </ul></p> <p>For the country 
                        Belgium, you can use one of these 3 ways to import: 
                        <ul> <li>Country: Belgium</li> <li>Country/Database 
                        ID: 21</li> <li>Country/External ID: base.be</li>
                        </ul></p> <p>According to your need, you should use 
                        one of these 3 ways to reference records in relations. 
                        Here is when you should use one or the other, 
                        according to your need: <ul> <li>Use Country: This is 
                        the easiest way when your data come from CSV files 
                        that have been created manually.</li> <li>Use 
                        Country/Database ID: You should rarely use this 
                        notation. It's mostly used by developers as it's main 
                        advantage is to never have conflicts (you may have 
                        several records with the same name, but they always 
                        have a unique Database ID)</li> <li>Use 
                        Country/External ID: Use External ID when you import 
                        data from a third party application.</li> </ul></p> 
                        <p>When you use External IDs, you can import CSV files 
                        with the "External ID" column to define the External 
                        ID of each record you import. Then, you will be able 
                        to make a reference to that record with columns like 
                        "Field/External ID". The following two CSV files give 
                        you an example for Products and their Categories.</p>
                        <a href="/base_import/static/csv/External_id_3rd_party_application_product_categories.csv">CSV file for categories</a><br/>
                        <a href="/base_import/static/csv/External_id_3rd_party_application_products.csv">CSV file for Products</a>
                    </dd>
                </dl>

                <dl>
                    <dt><a href="#" class="oe_import_toggle">
                        What can I do if I have multiple matches for a field?
                        </a></dt>
                    <dd>
                        <p>If for example you have two product categories 
                        with the child name "Sellable" (ie. "Misc. 
                        Products/Sellable" &amp; "Other Products/Sellable"),
                        your validation is halted but you may still import 
                        your data. However, we recommend you do not import the 
                        data because they will all be linked to the first 
                        'Sellable' category found in the Product Category list 
                        ("Misc. Products/Sellable"). We recommend you modify 
                        one of the duplicates' values or your product category 
                        hierarchy.<br/>
                        However if you do not wish to change your 
                        configuration of product categories, we recommend you 
                        use make use of the external ID for this field 
                        'Category'.</p>
                    </dd>
                </dl>

                <dl>
                    <dt><a href="#" class="oe_import_toggle">
                        How can I import a many2many relationship field 
                        (e.g. a customer that has multiple tags)?</a></dt>
                    <dd>
                        <p>The tags should be separated by a comma without any 
                        spacing. For example, if you want your customer to be 
                        linked to both tags 'Manufacturer' and 'Retailer' 
                        then you will encode "Manufacturer,
                        Retailer" in the same column of your CSV file.</p>
                        <a href="/base_import/static/csv/m2m_customers_tags.csv">
                        CSV file for Manufacturer, Retailer</a><br/>
                    </dd>
                </dl>

                <dl>
                    <dt><a href="#" class="oe_import_toggle">
                        How can I import a one2many relationship (e.g. several 
                        Order Lines of a Sales Order)?</a></dt>
                    <dd>
                        <p>If you want to import sales order having several 
                        order lines; for each order line, you need to reserve 
                        a specific row in the CSV file. The first order line 
                        will be imported on the same row as the information 
                        relative to order. Any additional lines will need an 
                        addtional row that does not have any information in 
                        the fields relative to the order.</p>
                        <p>As an example, here is 
                        purchase.order_functional_error_line_cant_adpat.CSV 
                        file of some quotations you can import, based on demo 
                        data.</p>
                        <a href="/base_import/static/csv/purchase.order_functional_error_line_cant_adpat.csv">File for some Quotations</a>
                        <p>The following CSV file shows how to import purchase 
                        orders with their respective purchase order lines:</p>
                        <a href="/base_import/static/csv/o2m_purchase_order_lines.csv">Purchase orders with their respective purchase order lines</a>
                        <p>The following CSV file shows how to import 
                        customers and their respective contacts</p>
                        <a href="/base_import/static/csv/o2m_customers_contacts.csv">Customers and their respective contacts</a>
                    </dd>
                </dl>


                <dl>
                    <dt><a href="#" class="oe_import_toggle">
                        Can I import several times the same record?</a></dt>
                    <dd>
                        <p>If you import a file that contains one of the 
                        column "External ID" or "Database ID", records that 
                        have already been imported will be modified instead of 
                        being created. This is very usefull as it allows you 
                        to import several times the same CSV file while having 
                        made some changes in between two imports. Odoo will 
                        take care of creating or modifying each record 
                        depending if it's new or not.</p> <p> This feature 
                        allows you to use the Import/Export tool of Odoo to 
                        modify a batch of records in your favorite spreadsheet 
                        application.</p>
                    </dd>
                </dl>

                <dl>
                    <dt><a href="#" class="oe_import_toggle">
                        What happens if I do not provide a value for a 
                        specific field?</a></dt>
                    <dd>
                        <p>If you do not set all fields in your CSV file, 
                        Odoo will assign the default value for every non 
                        defined fields. But if you
                        set fields with empty values in your CSV file, Odoo 
                        will set the EMPTY value in the field, instead of 
                        assigning the default value.</p>
                    </dd>
                </dl>

                <dl>
                    <dt><a href="#" class="oe_import_toggle">
                        How to export/import different tables from an SQL 
                        application to Odoo?</a></dt>
                    <dd>
                        <p>If you need to import data from different tables, 
                        you will have to recreate relations between records 
                        belonging to different tables. (e.g. if you import 
                        companies and persons, you will have to recreate the 
                        link between each person and the company they work 
                        for).</p> <p>To manage relations between tables, 
                        you can use the "External ID" facilities of Odoo. 
                        The "External ID" of a record is the unique identifier 
                        of this record in another application. This "External 
                        ID" must be unique accoss all the records of all 
                        objects, so it's a good practice to prefix this 
                        "External ID" with the name of the application or 
                        table. (like 'company_1', 'person_1' instead of '1')
                        </p> <p>As an example, suppose you have a SQL database 
                        with two tables you want to import: companies and 
                        persons. Each person belong to one company, so you 
                        will have to recreate the link between a person and 
                        the company he work for. (If you want to test this 
                        example, here is a <a href="/base_import/static/csv/database_import_test.sql">
                        dump of such a PostgreSQL database</a>).</p>
                        <p>We will first export all companies and their 
                        "External ID". In PSQL, write the following command:
                        </p> <p>&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;copy 
                        (select 'company_'||id as "External ID",company_name 
                        as "Name",'True' as "Is a Company" from companies) TO 
                        '/tmp/company.csv' with CSV HEADER;</p>
                        <p>This SQL command will create the following CSV file:
                        <br/>&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;External ID,Name,Is a Company
                        <br/>&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;company_1,Bigees,True
                        <br/>&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;company_2,Organi,True
                        <br/>&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;company_3,Boum,True</p>
                        <p>To create the CSV file for persons, linked to 
                        companies, we will use the following SQL command in 
                        PSQL:</p> <p>&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;copy (select 
                        'person_'||id as "External ID",person_name as 
                        "Name",'False' as "Is a Company",'company_'||company_id
                         as "Related Company/External ID" from persons) TO 
                        '/tmp/person.csv' with CSV</p>
                        <p>It will produce the following CSV file:
                        <br/>&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;External ID,Name,Is a 
                        Company,Related Company/External ID
                        <br/>&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;person_1,Fabien,False,company_1
                        <br/>&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;person_2,Laurence,False,company_1
                        <br/>&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;person_3,Eric,False,company_2
                        <br/>&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;person_4,Ramsy,False,company_3</p>
                        <p>As you can see in this file, Fabien and Laurence 
                        are working for the Bigees company (company_1) and 
                        Eric is working for the Organi company. The relation 
                        between persons and companies is done using the 
                        External ID of the companies. We had to prefix the 
                        "External ID" by the name of the table to avoid a 
                        conflict of ID between persons and companies (person_1 
                        and company_1 who shared the same ID 1 in the orignial 
                        database).</p>
                        <p>The two files produced are ready to be imported in 
                        Odoo without any modifications. After having 
                        imported these two CSV files, you will have 4 contacts 
                        and 3 companies. (the firsts two contacts are linked 
                        to the first company). You must first import the 
                        companies and then the persons.</p>
                    </dd>
                </dl>

            </div>
        </form>
    </t>

    <t t-name="ImportView.preview">
        <tr t-if="headers" class="oe_import_grid-header">
            <td t-foreach="headers" t-as="header" class="oe_import_grid-cell"
                ><t t-esc="header"/></td>
        </tr>
        <tr class="oe_import_fields">
            <!-- Iterate on first row to ensure we have all columns -->
            <td t-foreach="preview[0]" t-as="column">
                <input class="oe_import_match_field"/>
            </td>
        </tr>
        <tr t-foreach="preview" t-as="row" class="oe_import_grid-row">
            <td t-foreach="row" t-as="cell" class="oe_import_grid-cell"
                ><t t-esc="cell"/></td>
        </tr>
    </t>
    <t t-name="ImportView.preview.error">
        <p>Import preview failed due to: <t t-esc="error"/>. The issue is
            usually an incorrect file encoding.</p>
        <p>Here is the start of the file we could not import:</p>
        <pre><t t-esc="preview"/></pre>
    </t>
    <ul t-name="ImportView.error">
        <li t-foreach="errors" t-as="error"
            t-attf-class="oe_import_report oe_import_report_#{error_value[0].type}">
            <t t-call="ImportView.error.each">
                <t t-set="error" t-value="error_value[0]"/>
            </t>

            <a href="#" class="oe_import_report_count" t-if="error_value.length gt 1">
                <t t-esc="more(error_value.length - 1)"/>
            </a>
            <ul class="oe_import_report_more" t-if="error_value.length gt 1">
                <li t-foreach="error_value.length - 1" t-as="index">
                    <t t-call="ImportView.error.each">
                        <t t-set="error" t-value="error_value[index + 1]"/>
                    </t>
                </li>
            </ul>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <t t-name="ImportView.error.each">
        <span class="oe_import_report_message">
            <t t-esc="error.message"/>
        </span>
        <t t-if="error.rows"  t-esc="at(error.rows)"/>
        <t t-if="error.moreinfo" t-raw="info(error.moreinfo)"/>
    </t>
    <t t-extend="ListView.buttons">
        <t t-jquery="span.oe_alternative">
            this.attr('t-if', 'widget.options.import_enabled');
        </t>
        <t t-jquery="span.oe_alternative" t-operation="append">
            <a href="#" class="oe_bold oe_list_button_import">Import</a>
        </t>
    </t>
</templates>
